{"1167-ENT-DISTRICT": [{"number": 1, "question": "A business that fails to protect its employees from unnecessary risk or health hazards on the job may be sued for ", "choices": ["A. libel.", "B. misrepresentation.", "C. negligence.", "D. incompetence."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Negligence. A business might be sued for negligence if it does not take reasonable precautions to protect workers from risks or health hazards on the job. The basis of negligence is that the problems could have been easily avoided if the business had made some minor adjustments. Consequently, businesses usually try to make the workplace as safe as possible in order to avoid being sued for negligence. Misrepresentation involves making unrealistic claims about products. Libel is making false statements that harm an individual's reputation. Incompetence involves not having the skills or abilities necessary to perform satisfactorily. SOURCE: BL:001 SOURCE: FindLaw. (2017). Negligence. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://injury.findlaw.com/accident-injury-law/negligence.html "}, {"number": 2, "question": "What requirement of a legally enforceable contract requires that both of the parties who are entering into the contract are sane, sober, and of legal age? ", "choices": ["A. Genuineness of assent", "B. Consideration", "C. Capacity", "D. Legality of purpose"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Capacity. Certain conditions must be met for a contract to be legally enforceable. Capacity involves having the mental and cognitive ability to make and understand the agreement and the consequences of their actions. If one party is a child or is found to be mentally challenged or impaired, the contract is invalid and unenforceable. Consideration means that the agreement must include something of value that both parties bargain for. Genuineness of assent means that all parties know what they are agreeing to. Legality of purpose means that the agreement must not violate any laws. SOURCE: BL:002 SOURCE: Stim, R. (2017). Who lacks the capacity to contract? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.nolo.com/legal-encyclopedia/lack-capacity-to-contract-32647.html "}, {"number": 3, "question": "The owner receives all of the profits of the business and can act quickly in making business decisions when the form of business ownership is a ", "choices": ["A. corporation.", "B. partnership.", "C. joint venture.", "D. sole proprietorship."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Sole proprietorship. Other advantages of a sole proprietorship are that it is easy to start, it has certain tax advantages, and the details of the business can be kept private. In a partnership, the profits are divided among the partners who sometimes disagree as to how profits should be divided. In a corporation, the profits are divided among the stockholders. The officers of the corporation are responsible for the actual operation and management of the firm. A joint venture is an arrangement that involves two or more businesses entering into a relationship by combining complementary resources, such as technology, skills, capital, or distribution channels, for the benefit of all parties. SOURCE: BL:003 SOURCE: LAP-BL-001\u2014Own It Your Way (Types of Business Ownership) "}, {"number": 4, "question": "Which of the following is the type of tax that businesses are required to collect from customers when they purchase certain goods or services: ", "choices": ["A. Estate", "B. Income", "C. Sales", "D. Corporate"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Sales. Sales taxes are monies charged on sales of certain goods and services by state and/or local governments. The tax amount varies by location. After the business collects the sales tax from customers for their purchases, it pays the monies to the appropriate government agency. Income taxes are monies that the business withholds from its employees' wages. Estate taxes are monies that are collected from a person's estate upon his/her death. Corporations rather than customers pay corporate taxes. SOURCE: BL:009 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2017, April 27). Sales tax. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/salestax.asp "}, {"number": 5, "question": "Which of the following is a condition that must exist for channels to be effective: ", "choices": ["A. Channel members must not share tasks.", "B. They must have at least five members.", "C. Channel members must have varying goals.", "D. They must be properly managed."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "They must be properly managed. To be effective, channels must be properly managed. Channel members must share (not varying) common goals, and channel members must share tasks appropriately. Channels can be effective no matter how many members they have. SOURCE: CM:001 SOURCE: LAP-CM-002\u2014Chart Your Channels (Channel Management) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 14  "}, {"number": 6, "question": "Which of the following is a marketing function that can be performed by channel intermediaries: ", "choices": ["A. Promoting products", "B. Monitoring union activities", "C. Training employees", "D. Recruiting workers"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Promoting products. Channel intermediaries are persons or businesses that perform channel functions in an indirect channel of distribution. They can be responsible for such marketing functions as buying, selling, pricing, marking, storing, packaging, promoting, and financing. Recruiting workers for the business, training employees, and monitoring union activities are human resources activities, not marketing functions. SOURCE: CM:003 SOURCE: LAP-CM-003\u2014Channel It (Channels of Distribution)  "}, {"number": 7, "question": "A manufacturer of dishwashing soap has just invented a new type of soap that cleans better. The manufacturer should choose to distribute the soap through __________ distribution. ", "choices": ["A. intensive", "B. exclusive", "C. inclusive", "D. selective"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Intensive. Producers of consumer goods, such as dishwashing soap or candy, should use intensive distribution in order to make their product as available to consumers as possible. Exclusive distribution would make this product less available to the everyday consumer, as in the case of upscale cars or clothing, and is impractical for this type of product. Inclusive distribution is not a recognized distribution strategy. Selective distribution is a balance between intensive and exclusive distribution, such as the sale of certain power tools only through one or two retailers, and like exclusive distribution, is impractical for dishwashing soap. SOURCE: CM:010 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 504-505). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill.  "}, {"number": 8, "question": "What type of information does a well-written proposal include? ", "choices": ["A. Vague goals", "B. Specific benefits", "C. Previous trends", "D. Contingency data"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Specific benefits. A proposal is an informational document that presents the reader with a call to action. A proposal often suggests ways to solve a problem or to obtain information by taking a specific course of action. Because the proposal developer's goal is to get his/her suggestions implemented, a well-written proposal will tell the reader how s/he will benefit by implementing the procedures or using the data that the document provides. A well-written proposal does not necessarily include vague goals, previous trends, or contingency data. SOURCE: CO:062 SOURCE: Brandall, B. (2016, September 7). How to write a proposal and get what you want. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.process.st/how-to-write-a-proposal/  "}, {"number": 9, "question": "There are several auto repair shops in town, but Patricia's stands out. Her auto repair shop does great work, but what really sets her shop apart is the customer service. Every customer is greeted by a friendly employee, and s/he is given snacks and drinks while s/he waits for the repairs to be completed. The great customer service that people can expect from Patricia's business is considered her ", "choices": ["A. vision.", "B. tagline.", "C. brand promise.", "D. mission statement."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Brand promise. A business's brand promise is its (spoken or unspoken) agreement with its customers that it will consistently meet their expectations. When Patricia's customers visit her business, they know they'll receive outstanding customer service every time. A brand promise should go above and beyond goods and services and focus on something other businesses don't offer. For example, the other auto repair shops in town may do repairs that are just as good, but it's Patricia's outstanding customer service that sets her apart. A tagline is a company's slogan. Taglines often change based on marketing campaigns and cultural shifts, but a company's brand promise is permanent. A vision is the future a business desires to create. Providing great customer service may be part of Patricia's vision, but that alone is not a vision. A mission statement is a brief summary of what a business owner wants to be doing. This is not the same as a brand promise. SOURCE: CR:001 SOURCE: LAP-CR-006\u2014Share the Promise (Identifying Brand Promise) "}, {"number": 10, "question": "Financial loss from investing time and money to comply with accounting standards is an example of which strategic risk: ", "choices": ["A. Changing customer needs", "B. Reputation damage", "C. Regulatory and political issues", "D. Obsolescence"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Regulatory and political issues. Revenues and profits are affected by what governments require. Companies often have to invest time and money to comply with tax standards, environmental regulations, employee protection laws, and many other government guidelines. Financial loss from complying with accounting standards does not result from reputation damage, changing customer needs, or obsolescence. SOURCE: EC:011 SOURCE: LAP-EC-003\u2014Lose, Win, or Draw (Business Risk) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 15 "}, {"number": 11, "question": "The government's mandating the use of unleaded gas in new cars is an example of ", "choices": ["A. protecting specific businesses.", "B. protecting the environment.", "C. stabilizing the economy.", "D. providing public goods."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Protecting the environment. Unleaded gas is less harmful to the environment than leaded gas. Specific businesses are protected through subsidies or price supports. Public goods are items used by all people regardless of whether they can pay for them. The economy is stabilized through the government's monetary and fiscal policies. SOURCE: EC:008 SOURCE: LAP-EC-016\u2014Regulate and Protect (Government and Business) "}, {"number": 12, "question": "What type of business usually experiences economies of scale due to expanded operations? ", "choices": ["A. Large manufacturing plant", "B. Monopoly", "C. Individual financial planner", "D. Small local retailer"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Large manufacturing plant. Economies of scale is the concept that increasing the scale of production will lead to a decrease in the cost of production while increasing the output. This concept is often associated with large businesses, such as a large manufacturing plant, because the size of the facility makes it possible to produce more while spending less. Large plants usually are more specialized and have more equipment, which enables them to increase production. An individual financial planner and a small local retailer tend to be labor intensive and cannot afford the expense of equipment needed to gain economies of scale. A monopoly does not need to be concerned with its economies of scale since customers have nowhere else to obtain the product. SOURCE: EC:077 SOURCE: Heakal, R. (2017, April 19). What are economies of scale? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.investopedia.com/articles/03/012703.asp#axzz2DS4Azeprl "}, {"number": 13, "question": "Businesspeople who respect the unique customs and habits of their foreign customers are exhibiting ", "choices": ["A. communication skills.", "B. stereotypical behavior.", "C. cultural sensitivity.", "D. language differences."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Cultural sensitivity. Culture is the customs, habits, and traditions of a particular group of people. The way that different people interact with one another is an expression of their culture. Businesspeople need to be sensitive to the fact that their foreign customers may have unique customs such as bowing when they greet rather than shaking hands. They should accept these customs and try to make their foreign customers feel comfortable. Businesspeople who behave in this manner are showing respect for other customs and habits and are exhibiting cultural sensitivity. Communication skills are abilities to express yourself clearly and simply. Stereotypical behavior involves acting in a manner that conforms to a set image. Language differences occur when people speak different languages. SOURCE: EI:033 SOURCE: LAP-EI-011\u2014Getting to Know You (Cultural Sensitivity) "}, {"number": 14, "question": "\u201cYes, you'll save money instantly\u201d is an example of a statement with ", "choices": ["A. threatening language.", "B. an impersonal message.", "C. persuasive words.", "D. body language."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Persuasive words. \"Yes, you'll save money instantly\" uses several persuasive words. It is also directed to the person you're speaking with, instead of being an impersonal message. This statement does not demonstrate body language or threatening language. SOURCE: EI:012 SOURCE: LAP-EI-121\u2014Win Them Over (Persuading Others) "}, {"number": 15, "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of a self-confident leader: ", "choices": ["A. S/He has the ability to share a vision.", "B. S/He is truly invested in the work team.", "C. S/He is decisive, even in uncertain circumstances.", "D. S/He demonstrates empathy."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "S/He is decisive, even in uncertain circumstances. Self-confidence is a positive belief in your own talents, skills, and objectives. Self-confident leaders are decisive, even in uncertain circumstances. Being invested in the work team is a characteristic associated with responsibility. Demonstrating empathy is a characteristic associated with emotional intelligence. The ability to share a vision is a separate leadership characteristic. SOURCE: EI:009 SOURCE: LAP-EI-016\u2014Lead the Way (Concept of Leadership) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 16 "}, {"number": 16, "question": "Why is it important for team members to feel a sense of \"ownership\" and engagement in the vision? ", "choices": ["A. It's the only way they will become committed to it.", "B. Leaders cannot force compliance from them.", "C. They cannot be creative otherwise.", "D. They are responsible for determining the vision."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "It's the only way they will become committed to it. It's difficult to get people excited about a vision they don't really feel a part of. But when that vision is shared by the whole team, each member can feel personally invested in its success. Leaders may be able to force cooperation or compliance for a certain amount of time, but this will only result in low employee morale and, in the long run, will do nothing to further the vision. Only when team members feel the vision \"belongs\" to them as much as to the rest of the team or organization will they become truly committed to it. Team members are not necessarily responsible for determining the vision, and they may be talented creatively even if they are not fully committed. SOURCE: EI:060 SOURCE: LAP-EI-060\u2014Vision Quest (Enlisting Others in Vision) "}, {"number": 17, "question": "Which of the following statements is true regarding stakeholder expectations: ", "choices": ["A. Each group of stakeholders has different needs and expectations.", "B. Stakeholder expectations are always financially driven.", "C. All stakeholders want to exert authority over employees.", "D. Stakeholder expectations always come second to customer needs."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Each group of stakeholders has different needs and expectations. Stakeholders are people who are affected by a project's or business's success or failure. The needs and expectations of different groups of stakeholders depend on the individual perspectives of those stakeholders. Stakeholder expectations are not always financially driven. All stakeholders do not necessarily want to exert authority over employees; furthermore, employees are stakeholders. Stakeholder expectations do not always come second to customer needs; customers are stakeholders, and their expectations are considered alongside other stakeholders. SOURCE: EI:113 SOURCE: MacLellan, M. (2013, December 17). Defining, understanding, and meeting the needs of stakeholders. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.londonschoolofmarketing.com/blog/bid/360192/Defining-understanding-andmeeting-the-needs-of-stakeholders "}, {"number": 18, "question": "Julio is starting a new business, and he has formed relationships with several successful local business owners. Which of the following is the best way to leverage these relationships to help his own business succeed: ", "choices": ["A. Gaining inside marketing information", "B. Persistently asking those business owners to invest in his company", "C. Attending trade shows and conferences to make new connections", "D. Sharing those businesses' content on social media"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Sharing those businesses' content on social media. One way to leverage business relationships is to show other businesses how your business can provide value to them. Sharing content on social media helps show the businesses that Julio is willing to promote their content to others. In exchange, those businesses will be more likely to promote Julio's content in the future. Persistently asking those business owners to invest in his company might irritate the business owners and tarnish Julio's relationships with them. Attending trade shows and conferences to make new connections is a great way to build new relationships, but not necessarily to leverage existing relationships. Gaining inside marketing information from the other businesses is not necessarily ethical and would likely damage these business relationships in the long run. SOURCE: EI:116 SOURCE: Craig-Hart, S. (2016, November 1). 5 ways to help develop and leverage powerful business relationships. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://smartsimplemarketing.com/5- ways-to-help-develop-and-leverage-powerful-business-relationships "}, {"number": 19, "question": "Hazel started her own childcare network where she connects families to available babysitters at her school. Hazel could be described as a(n) ", "choices": ["A. direct salesperson.", "B. franchiser.", "C. wholesaler.", "D. entrepreneur."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Entrepreneur. An entrepreneur is anyone who creates, launches, organizes, and manages a new business and takes on the risk of that business. Hazel is an entrepreneur because she created and launched a new childcare business where she is accountable for risk. A franchiser is the owner of a business who gives the rights to operate a branch of that business to someone else in exchange for a fee and profits. A wholesaler is a merchant who sells to other businesses for resale or business use. A direct salesperson is someone who sells a product directly to customers. SOURCE: EN:039 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (p. 779). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 17 "}, {"number": 20, "question": "An entrepreneurial business owner must ", "choices": ["A. dislike business planning.", "B. be independently wealthy.", "C. desire regular 40-hour work weeks.", "D. have an adventurous spirit."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Have an adventurous spirit. Entrepreneurs must have an adventurous spirit because they assume a lot of risk and uncertainty, as well as experience excitement and spontaneity. Entrepreneurs do not necessarily have to be independently wealthy, though they should have enough in savings to survive at least a few years without turning a profit. Entrepreneurial business owners should not desire a regular 40-hour work week because entrepreneurs work long and irregular hours. Finally, entrepreneurial business owners need to plan ahead and account for all the resources they will need to start a new business. SOURCE: EN:040 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 779-780). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 21, "question": "What is one reason that it is easier than ever for small businesses to engage in international trade? ", "choices": ["A. Decreasing international middle class", "B. Technological advances", "C. Language barriers", "D. Increased regulation"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Technological advances. Due to the prevalence of the Internet and other technologies, it is easier for businesses of any size to engage in international trade. A rising international middle class, rather than a decreasing one, makes it easier than ever for small businesses to engage in international trade. Language barriers and increased regulation do not make it easier to engage in international trade. SOURCE: EN:041 SOURCE: Sarda, K. (2013, November 12). The secrets to taking your small business global. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.forbes.com/sites/groupthink/2013/11/12/the-secretsto-taking-your-small-business-global/#54f7280e2acf "}, {"number": 22, "question": "Which of the following is a global trend that might encourage an entrepreneur to consider international business opportunities: ", "choices": ["A. Higher allowances", "B. Lower tariffs", "C. Enforceable trade agreements", "D. Flexible currency rates"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Lower tariffs. A business opportunity is a circumstance that presents itself to provide a good or service. Entrepreneurs often find business opportunities by monitoring trends or the direction in which society is moving. One trend that positively affects international business is the lowering of trade barriers, including tariffs, which are taxes on import and export products. International trade is becoming more affordable and profitable because businesses do not pay as much in tariffs. Extreme changes in currency rates may influence a businessperson's decision to trade internationally, but currency rates always fluctuate somewhat, which indicates that fluctuations are not a trend. Trade agreements are not enforceable when a country does not want to participate. The reference to higher allowances is too general in nature to consider it a trend. SOURCE: EN:003 SOURCE: Dabla-Norris, E., & Duval, R. (2016, June 20). How lowering trade barriers can revive global productivity and growth. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://blogs.imf.org/2016/06/20/how-lowering-trade-barriers-can-revive-global-productivityand-growth/ "}, {"number": 23, "question": "Mara is facilitating a group brainstorming session to generate new product ideas for the company. Which of the following attitudes is important for Mara to demonstrate? ", "choices": ["A. Judgmental", "B. Neutral", "C. Passive", "D. Authoritarian"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Neutral. The goal of a group brainstorming session is to generate as many ideas as possible within a set amount of time. The facilitator's role is to guide the discussion and record the group's ideas. It is important for the facilitator to remain neutral or objective when group members share their ideas. By remaining objective and not judging or criticizing ideas, the facilitator helps the group feel comfortable and more willing to provide input. Part of the facilitator's role is to keep the group on track, so the facilitator should exhibit assertive behavior rather than a passive attitude. Exhibiting an authoritarian or rigid attitude may prevent group members from sharing their ideas. SOURCE: EN:006 SOURCE: Hawkins, C. (2008-2017). Meeting facilitation tips: Facilitating great meetings. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.makemeetingsmatter.com/articles/MeetingFacilitationTips.html Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 18 "}, {"number": 24, "question": "Landon wants to start a home-based T-shirt printing business. Which of the following are the most critical equipment and supplies that Landon will need to get his business up and running? ", "choices": ["A. T-shirts, thread, and display cases", "B. Printing machine, display cases, and T-shirts", "C. Artwork, T-shirts, and thread", "D. T-shirts, printing machine, and artwork"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "T-shirts, printing machine, and artwork. The requirements (e.g., time, money, and supplies) that a person needs to start a business differ and usually depend on the nature of the business. The basic requirements for starting a home-based T-shirt printing business are T-shirts, artwork to put on the Tshirts, and a printing machine to transfer the artwork to the T-shirts. Landon does not need thread or display cases to get this type of home-based business up and running. SOURCE: EN:009 SOURCE: Martin, M. (2017, July 19). What do I need to start a t-shirt business? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/need-start-t-shirt-business-2263.html "}, {"number": 25, "question": "A small-business owner might register for trademark protection for the company's ", "choices": ["A. computer software.", "B. invention.", "C. trade secret.", "D. logo."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Logo. A trademark is legal protection granted by the government to the owner, usually a business, of a distinctive symbol, mark, name, or motto. A company's logo may include a distinctive symbol, mark, or name, or a combination of the elements. A patent legally protects an invention. A trade secret is undisclosed information that is valuable to a business (e.g., customer lists). A copyright legally protects the owner of computer software. SOURCE: EN:013 SOURCE: United States Patent and Trademark Office. (2016, May). Protecting your trademark: Enhancing your rights through federal registration. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.uspto.gov/sites/default/files/documents/BasicFacts.pdf "}, {"number": 26, "question": "Evan does not want the legal obligation of repaying a loan and is willing to share profits with others. Which of the following options is Evan most likely to select to fund a new venture: ", "choices": ["A. Private equity", "B. Collateral savings", "C. Trade credit", "D. Community bank"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Private equity. When a start-up business owner obtains money in a way that s/he does not have debt, it is called private equity. This may include using personal savings, receiving money from friends and relatives, or soliciting support from private investors. Private investors generally expect a financial return on their investment. Credit and banks are debt-based ways to finance a business because these options involve repaying a loan. Collateral savings is a fictitious term. SOURCE: EN:016 SOURCE: Riley, J. (2015). Sources of finance for a startup or small business. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.tutor2u.net/business/reference/sources-of-finance-for-a-startup-orsmall-business "}, {"number": 27, "question": "What is a primary factor that small-business owners should consider when deciding to hire additional staff members? ", "choices": ["A. Interview techniques", "B. Payroll expenses", "C. Training methods", "D. Product standards"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Payroll expenses. A small-business owner considers many factors when determining if s/he should hire an employee. Payroll tends to be the largest expense for a business, so the small-business owner must determine how much or if s/he can afford to pay an employee. Payroll expenses include the employee's salary, taxes, health and disability insurance, benefits, etc. After the small-business owner decides to hire additional staff, s/he can determine the appropriate interview techniques and training methods to use. Product standards are a product management consideration rather than a staffing consideration. SOURCE: EN:018 SOURCE: Greene, C.L. (2011). Entrepreneurship: 21st century business (2nd ed.) [pp. 128-129]. Mason, OH: South Western Cengage Learning. "}, {"number": 28, "question": "Al is thinking about moving his company's headquarters to another city, which would be expensive but closer to the raw materials needed for manufacturing. The benefit in moving is ", "choices": ["A. demand.", "B. proximity.", "C. feasibility.", "D. independence."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Proximity. Resources are the items or people that a business uses to accomplish a goal or to make a product. Small-business owners must consider both the costs and the benefits in obtaining resources, such as hiring a new employee, contracting a transportation company, or obtaining raw materials for manufacturing. If Al moves the company's headquarters, the costs are the possibility of losing good employees and the financial burden associated with a large move. The benefit of moving is the proximity, or being closer to the raw materials the company needs to manufacture its products. The benefit of being closer is that communication might improve due to the proximity, and the company may save transportation costs since the raw materials are closer to the manufacturing equipment. Demand, feasibility, and independence are not benefits for moving the company. SOURCE: EN:021 SOURCE: Bamford, C.E., & Bruton, G.D. (2011). Entrepreneurship: A small business approach (p. 78). New York: The McGraw-Hill Companies, Inc. Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 19 "}, {"number": 29, "question": "All of a firm's activities and how they function in relation to one another are known as ", "choices": ["A. business operations.", "B. efficiency standards.", "C. communication goals.", "D. desired outputs."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Business operations. Business operations are all of the functions that keep a business running. Inventory management, financial activities, advertising, sales, human resources management, and distribution are important functions that keep a business going. For example, a business functions more efficiently when the appropriate inventory is in stock because the product is available to sell and to ship to the customers. Efficiency standards, various goals, and outputs are elements of the business operations. SOURCE: EN:023 SOURCE: Kiisel, T. (2015, July 22). What is operations? And why does my business need it? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.ondeck.com/blog/what-is-operations/ "}, {"number": 30, "question": "Because the MBC Company has one location that services the eastern part of the country and another location that services the western part of the country, the company's work flow is organized by ", "choices": ["A. relationship.", "B. work teams.", "C. authority.", "D. territory."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Territory. Work flow is the order in which information is shared, tasks are performed, and decisions are made in relation to activities that keep a business running. A business organizes its work flow in a manner that best suits the nature of the business and its goals. One way to organize work flow is to divides work-related tasks by geographic location, such as territory or region. When a business organizes groups to do specific short- or long-term projects, work flow is organized in work teams. Authority and relationship are not widely used terms that businesses use to describe work flow organization methods. SOURCE: EN:027 SOURCE: Bamford, C.E., & Bruton, G.D. (2011). Entrepreneurship: A small business approach (pp. 159-161). New York: The McGraw-Hill Companies, Inc. "}, {"number": 31, "question": "Looking at problems from various points of view helps a small-business owner develop ", "choices": ["A. practical arguments.", "B. creative solutions.", "C. unnecessary conflicts.", "D. unpredictable results."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Creative solutions. Creative problem solving is the process of finding solutions to issues or obstacles (problems) by generating unique ideas or approaches. To generate unique ideas or approaches, smallbusiness owners use creative-thinking techniques, which often involve looking at problems or issues from different points of view. For example, a business might have a problem with a distribution process. The owner might look at the problem from a shipping department employee's perspective, a customer's perspective, or an intermediary's perspective to find a way to solve the problem. Business owners do not look at problems from various points of view to develop arguments, conflicts, or unpredictable results. SOURCE: EN:029 SOURCE: Cleverism.com. (2015, September 26). Why creativity is so crucial for entrepreneurs? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.cleverism.com/why-creativity-is-so-crucialfor-entrepreneurs/ "}, {"number": 32, "question": "Ellen wants to step back from the day-to-day activities of running her company. She decides to take the company to another level by selling public stock. One way Ellen can stay involved in the company is by ", "choices": ["A. arranging a tactical acquisition.", "B. appointing a family member as president.", "C. serving on the board of directors.", "D. hiring her successor."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Serving on the board of directors. By taking the company \"public,\" Ellen is beginning the \"IPO\" (initial public offering) process. IPO means that the business owner is selling stock to the public and giving up control of some or all of the business; over time, the venture becomes a public corporation. By incorporating the business, the owner is selling stock to anyone who wants to buy into the company. When a business becomes a public corporation, it must follow strict government rules and regulations, including forming a board of directors to guide the corporation. Sometimes, to stay somewhat involved in the business, the business owner (entrepreneur) will serve on the board of directors. Being a board member often makes the transition or exit process smoother. The board appoints the corporation's president or successor, so Ellen does not have total control over that activity. Tactical acquisition is a fictitious term. SOURCE: EN:036 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2015, December 16). Board of directors - B of D. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.investopedia.com/terms/b/boardofdirectors.asp "}, {"number": 33, "question": "Which of the following categories of information are found on a balance sheet: ", "choices": ["A. Income, expenditures, profit", "B. Assets, liabilities, owner's equity", "C. Assets, liabilities, margin", "D. Revenues, expenses, profit"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Assets, liabilities, owner's equity. A balance sheet is a financial statement that captures the financial condition of the business at that particular moment. The statement first lists assets, anything of value that a business owns; then liabilities, or debts, that the business owes; and finally owner's equity, or the amount the owner has invested in the business, plus or minus profits and losses. Revenues, or income; expenses, or expenditures; and profit are components of an income statement, or profit-and-loss statement. Margin is a term that describes the difference between net sales and cost of goods sold. SOURCE: FI:085 SOURCE: LAP-FI-085\u2014Show Me the Money (Nature of Accounting) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 20 "}, {"number": 34, "question": "The balance sheet has a close relationship with the company's ", "choices": ["A. mortgage.", "B. income statement.", "C. fair market value.", "D. statement of financial position."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Income statement. The balance sheet has a close relationship with the company's income statement. Changes to the income statement directly affect the numbers on the balance sheet. The balance sheet shows the company's mortgage as a liability, but the two are not closely related. The company's value on the balance sheet is quite different from its fair market value. Statement of financial position is another name for the balance sheet. SOURCE: FI:093 SOURCE: LAP-FI-010\u2014The Right Balance (The Nature of Balance Sheets) "}, {"number": 35, "question": "Which of the following phrases effectively describes a business's income statement: ", "choices": ["A. Income preview", "B. Budget estimate", "C. Cash-flow report", "D. Financial picture"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Financial picture. A business's income statement summarizes where the business's money came from and where it went. It is an entire financial picture that lists all revenue and expenses for a certain time period, usually one year. An income statement includes information used in budgets and cash-flow reports. It is a picture of a business's financial status, rather than a prediction of the financial future. SOURCE: FI:094 SOURCE: LAP-FI-004\u2014Watch Your Bottom Line (Income Statements) "}, {"number": 36, "question": "Managerial accounting differs from financial accounting because managerial accounting ", "choices": ["A. helps people within a business rather than outside of the organization.", "B. does not focus on planning and budgeting.", "C. is governed by federal regulation.", "D. has less impact on decision-making."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Helps people within a business rather than outside of the organization. Managerial accounting is focused on providing financial information for internal organizational use. In contrast, financial accounting information is used outside of the organization. Managerial accounting does focus on planning and budgeting. Financial accounting, rather than managerial accounting, is governed by federal regulation. Finally, managerial accounting has more impact on decision-making than financial accounting because it is used within the organization as decisions are made. SOURCE: FI:657 SOURCE: Jan, I. (2011-2013). Managerial accounting. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://accountingexplained.com/managerial/introduction/ "}, {"number": 37, "question": "One reason why banks might be reluctant to lend money to a start-up business is because the business ", "choices": ["A. has a solid business plan.", "B. will not have collateral.", "C. has no record of repaying loans.", "D. must incorporate first."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Has no record of repaying loans. Banks look at many factors to determine if a business is worthy of credit. Start-up businesses borrow money based on the entrepreneur's past record of loan repayment because the business is new and has no previous debt repayment record. If a business incorporates, other avenues of securing capital are available. If start-up businesses have sufficient collateral and a solid business plan, it is easier for them to obtain financing from a bank. SOURCE: FI:034 SOURCE: Carabelli, C. (2012, April 9). What do banks look at for loans? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/banks-look-loans-42003.html "}, {"number": 38, "question": "When a business has been running successfully for several years, what would be a probable next financial step? ", "choices": ["A. Purchasing a second location", "B. Acquiring start-up funds", "C. Deciding on financial goals", "D. Determining product prices"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Purchasing a second location. If a business has been running successfully for several years, it may be in the expansion stage of its lifecycle. This could mean that the company would consider purchasing a second location. The company would acquire start-up funds, decide on financial goals, and determine product prices at a much earlier stage in development. SOURCE: FI:339 SOURCE: Ryan, K. (2015, March 23). The 4 stages of the business lifecycle and how to recognize what you need next. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.roseryan.com/blog/2015/03/the-4-stages-of-the-business-lifecycle/ "}, {"number": 39, "question": "Marginal analysis is a cost/benefit decision process that seeks to determine ", "choices": ["A. the best qualities to look for in potential employees.", "B. how a manager can cut costs.", "C. the likely returns on a new investment.", "D. profit-maximizing quantity of output."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Profit-maximizing quantity of output. Marginal analysis compares marginal cost and marginal revenue to determine the amount of output that produces the greatest profits. It does not help determine how a manager can cut costs. Although it might help an investor to choose among investments, it does not determine the likely returns on a particular, new investment. And, although it might help determine the optimal number of employees, it does not determine the best qualities to look for in potential employees. SOURCE: FI:358 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2015, June 12). Marginal analysis. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.investopedia.com/terms/m/marginal-analysis.asp Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 21 "}, {"number": 40, "question": "What sales forecasting technique creates accurate forecasts for individual products? ", "choices": ["A. Sales force composite", "B. Delphi", "C. Survey of buyer intentions", "D. Jury of executive opinion"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Sales force composite. There are several advantages to the sales force composite. More accurate forecasts for individual products can usually be obtained because sales personnel have first-hand knowledge about demand for certain products as a result of their constant contact with customers. It is an inexpensive method to use because it has few costs other than the time required. It also provides as much detail as the business might need because the business can forecast sales for individual products and for an overall company sales forecast. The Delphi sales-forecasting method can take a lot of time; therefore, it is expensive. The survey of buyer intentions sales forecasting method is not always accurate since customers sometimes can't make accurate predictions of their buying intentions. The jury of executive opinion sales forecasting method may be too optimistic or too conservative depending upon the executives' viewpoints. Therefore, some forecasters consider this a form of guesswork, thereby requiring the use of other forecasting methods to support it. SOURCE: FI:096 SOURCE: Insight Central. (2011, February 10). Forecast Friday topic: Expert judgment. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://analysights.wordpress.com/tag/sales-force-compositeforecasts/ "}, {"number": 41, "question": "An example of an operating expense that is included in a business's income statement is ", "choices": ["A. inventory.", "B. purchases.", "C. commissions.", "D. allowances."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Commissions. Commission is a percentage of the total sale amount paid to the individual who makes the sale. Many businesses pay a commission to salespeople, which is part of their salary. Salaries and wages are operating expenses that are listed in a business's income statement. Purchases and value of inventory are included in the cost of merchandise sold category of an income statement. Allowances are deductions that are indicated in the revenue category of an income statement. SOURCE: FI:102 SOURCE: Kennon, J. (2017, May 29). Operating expense on the income statement. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.thebalance.com/operating-expense-on-the-incomestatement-357586 "}, {"number": 42, "question": "Which of the following financial analysis methods is used to show the relationship of each component to the total within a single financial statement: ", "choices": ["A. Fundamental analysis", "B. Horizontal analysis", "C. Industry analysis", "D. Vertical analysis"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Vertical analysis. Vertical analysis is often used to show the relationship of each component to the total within a single financial statement. Horizontal analysis is a comparison of the same items on a company's financial statements for two or more periods. Businesses often compare their financial results with industry standards or averages to determine how well they are actually performing. Fundamental analysis involves studying all aspects of a company in an effort to understand its intrinsic value. SOURCE: FI:334 SOURCE: CCD Consultants. (2009-2015). Financial ratios interpretation. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.ccdconsultants.com/calculators/financial-ratios/financial-ratiosanalysis-and-interpretation?tab=interpretation "}, {"number": 43, "question": "What staffing activity involves seeking out and attracting qualified potential job candidates? ", "choices": ["A. Training", "B. Recruiting", "C. On-boarding", "D. Interviewing"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Recruiting. The part of staffing that involves seeking out and attracting qualified potential job candidates is called recruiting. HR managers have many different methods for recruitment, and they will choose the ones that are most appropriate to their industry and the position(s) available. Training is an HR management activity that ensures employees are knowledgeable and productive. On-boarding is an HR management activity that gets a new employee started on the job. Interviewing comes after recruiting\u2014 recruiting produces potential candidates to interview. SOURCE: HR:410 SOURCE: LAP-HR-035\u2014People Pusher (Nature of Human Resources Management) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 22 "}, {"number": 44, "question": "To screen job applications and employment r\u00e9sum\u00e9s, a business might use computer software that conducts text searches to scan for ", "choices": ["A. typographical errors.", "B. salary requirements.", "C. numerical ratings.", "D. key words."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Key words. Many large businesses must handle several hundred applications and r\u00e9sum\u00e9s. To save time and money, these businesses screen applicants for open positions by using computer software that scans the application or r\u00e9sum\u00e9 and searches for key words that the business selects when establishing job criteria. For example, if a business needs to fill a position that requires certain computer software knowledge, the business might select the name of the software as a key word. Then, human resources personnel review the documents that contain the key words and examine them in more detail. A text search might include salary requirements, numerical ratings, and typographical errors, but businesses do not always request this type of information, which may be difficult to capture accurately. SOURCE: HR:354 SOURCE: Ideal. (2016, October 26). Resume screening: A how-to guide for recruiters. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://ideal.com/resume-screening/ "}, {"number": 45, "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of hiring the right employee for a job: ", "choices": ["A. Increased employee turnover", "B. Increased risk of poor job performance", "C. Decreased employee morale", "D. Decreased cost of selection"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Decreased cost of selection. Careful selection of employees can save money through reduced costs associated with hiring and training and through increased levels of productivity. Other benefits of good employee selection are reduced risk of poor employee morale, reduced risk of poor job performance, reduced employee turnover, and time savings. SOURCE: HR:356 SOURCE: Le Maire, N. (2014, August 26). The importance of hiring the right people. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://newtohr.com/importance-hiring-right-people/ "}, {"number": 46, "question": "One of the advantages to businesses of training staff is that it tends to increase ", "choices": ["A. employee satisfaction.", "B. operating expense.", "C. compensation.", "D. feedback."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Employee satisfaction. An advantage of training staff is that it tends to increase employee satisfaction. Employees who have the training to do their jobs correctly usually perform well on the job and are satisfied with their situation. If employees do not have the necessary training, they may become discouraged and unmotivated. Dissatisfied employees often are not productive because it is difficult for them to work effectively. Training may increase operating expenses which is a disadvantage of training. Training does not necessarily increase compensation or feedback. SOURCE: HR:392 SOURCE: McNamara, C. (n.d.). Employee training and development: Reasons and benefits. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://managementhelp.org/training/basics/reasons-fortraining.htm "}, {"number": 47, "question": "Which of the following is an example of an employee complaint that is related to a coworker: ", "choices": ["A. Sam complains to his production manager that the new materials are jamming the equipment.", "B. Kelly advises Joe that a flaw in the computer system is creating inefficiencies in her department.", "C. Ann tells her boss that Brad talks loudly on the phone and distracts her ability to focus on work.", "D. Mario confides in Paige that he disagrees with the wage freeze that the company has instituted."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Ann tells her boss that Brad talks loudly on the phone and distracts her ability to focus on work. Employees complain about a variety of different things in the workplace. Sometimes, a coworker's habits are an issue with employees. In many situations, these problems can be resolved quickly and easily. In this situation, Ann works in close proximity to a loud talker, which is distracting her, so Ann has a valid complaint about a coworker. Ann or her boss can simply ask Brad to lower his voice. Inefficiencies with a computer system and problems with machinery are complaints about the business's processes or operations. Mario's complaint is about the company's salary policies. SOURCE: HR:366 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (p. 263). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 48, "question": "XYZ Company is interested in developing, producing, and selling a new product. Before it does so, the company spends six months conducting marketing research. What are the primary advantages of this course of action? ", "choices": ["A. To delay the production process and increase labor costs", "B. To increase costs and determine consumer dislikes", "C. To predict trends and provide information to customers", "D. To determine customer preferences and minimize losses"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "To determine customer preferences and minimize losses. Businesses obtain marketing information in order to develop a product that customers want and need. By doing research, companies obtain marketing information that helps them to minimize the losses that may occur from introducing a product that customers do not want. Businesses do not conduct marketing research to increase costs, although they may identify consumer dislikes. The goal is not to delay production or increase labor costs. Marketing research may identify trends, but it is not intended to provide information to customers. SOURCE: IM:012 SOURCE: LAP-IM-012\u2014Data Do It! (Need for Marketing Data) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 23 "}, {"number": 49, "question": "Which of the following is essential to all marketing research: ", "choices": ["A. Frequency", "B. Primary data", "C. Accuracy", "D. Secondary data"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Accuracy. Accuracy is absolutely essential in gathering, recording, and analyzing marketing-research data if the data are to be of value to the business. Inaccurate data can cause the business to make incorrect or unwise decisions. The frequency with which research is conducted would depend upon the needs of the business. Primary data are facts collected specifically for the problem or project at hand. Secondary data are facts that have been collected for purposes other than the project at hand. A marketing-research project may require either or both kinds of data. SOURCE: IM:010 SOURCE: LAP-IM-010\u2014Seek and Find (Marketing Research) "}, {"number": 50, "question": "The marketing function that helps marketers make decisions about what and to whom to sell is ", "choices": ["A. marketing-information management.", "B. product/service management.", "C. transportation.", "D. promotion."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Marketing-information management. This function involves gathering, accessing, synthesizing, evaluating, and disseminating information for use in making business decisions. Promotion is a marketing function that communicates information about goods, services, images, and/or ideas to achieve a desired outcome. Product/Service management involves obtaining, developing, maintaining, and improving a product or service mix in response to market opportunities. Transportation is the physical movement of products from one location to another or the method by which they are moved. SOURCE: MK:002 SOURCE: LAP-MK-001\u2014Work the Big Seven (Marketing Functions) "}, {"number": 51, "question": "A neighborhood grocery store has added a bakery. What element of marketing should the store use to attract customers from surrounding areas? ", "choices": ["A. Product", "B. Price", "C. Place", "D. Promotion"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Promotion. The promotion element of marketing refers to the various types of strategies that marketers use to communicate information about goods, services, images, and/or ideas to achieve a desired outcome. Product refers to what goods, services, or ideas will be offered to customers. Price involves determining and adjusting prices to maximize return and meet customers' perceptions of value. Place, or distribution, involves moving, storing, locating, and/or transferring ownership of goods and services. SOURCE: MP:001 SOURCE: LAP-MP-002\u2014Pick the Mix (Nature of Marketing Strategies) "}, {"number": 52, "question": "In order for a market to exist, consumers must have an unfulfilled desire for a product and ", "choices": ["A. know who makes the product.", "B. know where the product is sold.", "C. have financial resources.", "D. have a specific brand preference."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Have financial resources. A market is a customer or a potential customer who has an unfulfilled desire and is financially able and willing to satisfy that desire. Consumers' brand preferences are not a factor. Knowing who makes the product or where it is sold are not necessary to the existence of a market. SOURCE: MP:003 SOURCE: LAP-MP-003\u2014Have We Met? (Market Identification) "}, {"number": 53, "question": "An important criterion to consider when identifying market segments is the __________ of the market. ", "choices": ["A. age", "B. size", "C. gender", "D. occupation"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Size. When identifying market segments, it is necessary to consider various criteria. An important criterion is the size of the market because there must be a sufficient number of people in the market for it to provide a good profit potential. Today, many small markets are increasing in size and attracting the attention of businesses because there is a lot of potential for growth. An example is ethnic market segments that are becoming significant. Age, gender, and occupation are demographic characteristics of a market rather than criteria for identifying market segments. SOURCE: MP:004 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 43-49). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 54, "question": "What is a potential weakness a manager might identify in a SWOT analysis? ", "choices": ["A. High-quality products", "B. Lack of management depth", "C. Competitors failing", "D. Low-cost foreign competition"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Lack of management depth. A SWOT analysis identifies possible strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, and threats. A lack of management depth is a potential weakness that a manager might identify. Highquality products are examples of a potential strength. Competitors failing is an example of potential opportunity. Low-cost foreign competition is an example of a potential threat. SOURCE: MP:010 SOURCE: LAP-MP-004\u2014Analyze This! (SWOT Analysis) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 24 "}, {"number": 55, "question": "As part of their marketing plans, what do businesses develop first that are intended to lead to increased sales and revenue? ", "choices": ["A. Objectives", "B. Strategies", "C. Tactics", "D. Activities"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Objectives. Objectives are goals the business wants the marketing plan to reach. The objectives in a marketing plan are intended to lead to increased sales and revenue. When preparing its marketing plan, a business first develops specific objectives to follow that should be clear and measurable and that should be achieved in a certain amount of time. For example, a business will be able to monitor its expanded advertising program in order to determine if sales and revenue are increasing by the desired amount. If sales and revenue do not increase by 10% in one year, the business will be able to revise its marketing plan and establish new objectives. A business develops objectives before it develops strategies, tactics, and activities which are intended to achieve the objectives. SOURCE: MP:018 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 37-41). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 56, "question": "Which of the following is a specification that a business might establish for selecting spreadsheet software programs: ", "choices": ["A. Electronically communicate data", "B. Graphically display financial information", "C. Regularly organize customer information", "D. Digitally produce marketing data"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Graphically display financial information. Businesses establish specifications for selecting spreadsheet software in order to obtain the type of programs that will meet their needs. This is important because not all spreadsheet software programs have the same capabilities, such as graphically displaying financial information. Some businesses may need only simple graphics in the form of graphs or charts, while others need sophisticated graphics that will display financial information in a variety of visual formats. Communications software is used to electronically communicate data. Database software is used to regularly organize customer information. Word processing and graphic design programs are used to produce marketing data. SOURCE: NF:091 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 214-215). New York: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 57, "question": "How long are businesses required to keep their records? ", "choices": ["A. On a seasonal basis", "B. Varies greatly", "C. Indefinitely", "D. One year"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Varies greatly. The length of time that businesses use and store their records can vary greatly. Some businesses will use certain records indefinitely, while other businesses might maintain information on a seasonal basis or for only one year. The law often determines how long certain records must be maintained. SOURCE: NF:001 SOURCE: Burrow, J.L. (2012). Marketing (3rd ed.) [p. 349]. Mason, OH: South-Western, Cengage Learning. "}, {"number": 58, "question": "Businesses often conduct environmental scans to determine if they should ", "choices": ["A. make staffing adjustments.", "B. expand into other markets.", "C. follow government regulations.", "D. improve their computer systems."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Expand into other markets. An environmental scan is a study of the external forces that influence a business's success. An environmental scan examines the business's competitors; social issues and trends; and government, political, and economic factors. An environmental scan provides information that helps the business make decisions, such as whether it should expand into other markets. Staffing adjustments and computer improvements are internal factors that a business considers when it wants to enhance its productivity. A business should always follow government regulations. SOURCE: NF:015 SOURCE: LAP-NF-015\u2014Get the 4-1-1 (Conducting an Environmental Scan) "}, {"number": 59, "question": "What is a benefit to a tour operator who makes business decisions by analyzing statistical information? ", "choices": ["A. Improved performance", "B. Lower demand", "C. Increased competition", "D. Lower outputs"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Improved performance. Statistics are information presented in numerical form. Businesses analyze and interpret statistics to make various business decisions. By analyzing statistical information, a tour operator might determine ways in which to improve sales, productivity (higher outputs), or overall performance in order to compete more effectively in the marketplace. Lower demand, increased competition, and lower outputs do not benefit tour operators. SOURCE: NF:093 SOURCE: Bianca, A. (2011, August 15). The advantages of statistics in business. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/advantages-statistics-business-18698.html Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 25 "}, {"number": 60, "question": "Because operations managers control so much of a business's money, they must focus on ", "choices": ["A. keeping costs low.", "B. hiring the best employees.", "C. creating effective advertising campaigns.", "D. generating publicity."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Keeping costs low. Because operations managers control so much of a business's money, they must focus on keeping costs low. Operations managers are not responsible for hiring employees, creating advertising campaigns, or generating publicity. SOURCE: OP:189 SOURCE: LAP-OP-189\u2014Smooth Operations (Nature of Operations) "}, {"number": 61, "question": "Obtaining goods that will satisfy the needs and wants of a business's customers is a function of ", "choices": ["A. advertising.", "B. selling.", "C. marketing.", "D. purchasing."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Purchasing. Purchasing is a business function which involves the planning and procedures necessary to obtain goods and services for use in the business or for resale. Personal selling is planned, personalized communication designed to influence purchase behavior and to ensure satisfaction. Advertising is any paid form of nonpersonal presentation of goods, services, or ideas. Marketing is an organizational function and a set of processes for creating, communicating, and delivering value to customers and for managing customer relations in ways that benefit the organization and its stakeholders. SOURCE: OP:015 SOURCE: LAP-OP-002\u2014Buy Right (Purchasing) "}, {"number": 62, "question": "Why is it important for businesses to have efficient production? ", "choices": ["A. To be competitive", "B. To remain flexible", "C. To pay employees", "D. To buy resources"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "To be competitive. Businesses must have efficient production in order to be competitive. Efficient production turns out the maximum number of products at the lowest cost. If the business's costs of production are higher than its competitors' costs, the business will have to set its prices higher than competitors' prices. This is likely to reduce sales. Businesses do not have efficient production in order to buy resources or pay employees, although efficient production generates the profit that makes it possible for businesses to buy additional resources and pay employees. A business's production may or may not be flexible depending on the type of business. SOURCE: OP:017 SOURCE: LAP-OP-017\u2014Can You Make It? (Nature of Production) "}, {"number": 63, "question": "What do managers need to do to develop and maintain the level of quality that customers expect? ", "choices": ["A. Obtain industry information", "B. Monitor all aspects of the business", "C. Consider the type of competition", "D. Prepare an operating budget"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Monitor all aspects of the business. It is important for a business's management team to monitor all aspects of the business so it can maintain or exceed the quality level that its customers expect. Monitoring business activities will enable managers to identify and correct potential problems before they have a negative impact on the level of quality. If quality decreases, the business may lose customers to its competitors. Obtaining industry information, considering the type of competition, and preparing an operating budget will not help a business to develop and maintain the level of quality that customers expect. SOURCE: OP:020 SOURCE: Colgate, A. (2017). Total quality management's impact on different business processes. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.businessdictionary.com/article/631/totalquality-managements-impact-on-different-business-processes/ "}, {"number": 64, "question": "Expenses such as payroll and rent that are necessary to the running of a business are called __________ expenses. ", "choices": ["A. operating", "B. fixed", "C. variable", "D. liability"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Operating. Operating expenses include variable and fixed expenses. Variable expenses may be different from month to month, e.g., payroll and supplies. These are directly affected by production or sales. Fixed expenses, on the other hand, remain the same for an extended period of time, e.g., mortgage or rent. A liability is a debt owed either short-term (due in the current fiscal year) or long-term. SOURCE: OP:024 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2009). Marketing essentials (pp. 767-769). Woodland Hills, CA: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 26 "}, {"number": 65, "question": "A business negotiates a two-year lease on 2,250 square feet of space for $2.60 per square foot with an option on a third year at a 5% increase in rent. What will the monthly rent be if the business extends the lease for a third year? ", "choices": ["A. $6,265.50", "B. $5,976.00", "C. $5,850.00", "D. $6,142.50"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "$6,142.50. Businesses often negotiate leases for a certain amount of square feet and for a certain number of years with an option to renew. To calculate the monthly rent for the third year, first determine the current monthly rent by multiplying square footage by the rate (2,250 x $2.60 = $5,850). Then, multiply that amount by the 5% increase ($5,850 x 5% or .05 = $292.50). Add the amount of the increase to the current rent to determine the monthly rent for the third year ($5,850.00 + $292.50 = $6,142.50). SOURCE: OP:028 SOURCE: Sadler, D. (2010, August 28). Should you buy or lease your business facility? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.allbusiness.com/should-you-buy-or-lease-yourbusiness-facility-15051483-1.html "}, {"number": 66, "question": "Most company budgets are based on ", "choices": ["A. net profit.", "B. expenses.", "C. sales.", "D. gross profit."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Sales. Once the company has predicted its ability to generate sales, individual budgets are then prepared for other activities such as advertising, merchandising, purchasing, administration, and labor. The business needs to estimate sales before it can budget for expenses. Net profit is the money remaining after operating expenses are subtracted from gross profit, which is the money left after the costs of goods expense is subtracted from total income. SOURCE: OP:030 SOURCE: WikiHow. (2017, March 13). How to create a business budget. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.wikihow.com/Create-a-Business-Budget "}, {"number": 67, "question": "Which of the following situations would supply chain managers encounter during the final stage of supply chain management: ", "choices": ["A. A customer returns a defective product.", "B. The company finds reliable suppliers.", "C. The business plans to deliver goods to customers.", "D. Managers develop a supply chain strategy."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "A customer returns a defective product. In the final stage of supply chain management, customers may return defective products. Finding reliable suppliers, planning to deliver goods to customers, and developing a supply chain strategy would all occur during earlier stages of supply chain management. SOURCE: OP:303 SOURCE: Venus, D., Joseph, A., & Oppenheimer, L. (2017, August 24). What is supply chain management? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.wisegeek.com/what-issupply-chain-management.htm "}, {"number": 68, "question": "What is Claire doing when she reviews a report that compares the purchase transactions of the company's four largest customers? ", "choices": ["A. Conducting a sales analysis", "B. Preparing a purchasing forecast", "C. Organizing an inventory report", "D. Analyzing service performance"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Conducting a sales analysis. Businesses collect information to analyze all of their business functions. Sales are typically a business's primary source of income. Businesses review many aspects of sales to analyze and compare product movement, customer activity, salesperson performance, etc. Claire is not preparing a purchasing forecast, organizing an inventory report, or analyzing service performance. SOURCE: OP:327 SOURCE: Nielsen, L. (2010, August 12). Define sales analysis. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/define-sales-analysis-5258.html "}, {"number": 69, "question": "Business process thinking is meant to help companies ", "choices": ["A. achieve goals and serve customers.", "B. hire employees and fill roles.", "C. process payroll and compensate employees.", "D. enforce safety standards."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Achieve goals and serve customers. Business process thinking is meant to help a company work more efficiently and achieve goals. It is also customer-focused. The main goal of business process thinking is not to hire employees and fill roles, process payroll and compensate employees, or enforce safety standards. SOURCE: OP:474 SOURCE: Hammer, M. (n.d.) Business process thinking check list. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.1000advices.com/guru/processes_thinking_13q_mh.html "}, {"number": 70, "question": "When bottlenecks in business processes develop that cause a company to miss deadlines and waste resources, an effective manager would most likely choose to ", "choices": ["A. invest in quality control.", "B. redesign the business processes.", "C. implement an employee incentive program.", "D. speed up production."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Redesign the business processes. When bottlenecks in business processes develop, an effective manager would most likely redesign the business processes to eliminate the bottlenecks. Investing in quality control, implementing an employee incentive program, and/or speeding up production would not eliminate the bottlenecks. SOURCE: OP:475 SOURCE: Mind Tools. (1996-2017). Improving business processes. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.mindtools.com/pages/article/improving-business-processes.htm Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 27 "}, {"number": 71, "question": "One of the main external factors that may cause a firm to change its business processes is ", "choices": ["A. desire for growth.", "B. competition.", "C. low employee morale.", "D. high operating costs."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Competition. Competition is one of the main external factors that may cause a firm to change its businesses processes. Although desire for growth, low employee morale, and high operating costs are reasons to change business processes, these are all internal factors. SOURCE: OP:476 SOURCE: Joseph, C. (2010, June 7). Factors that may cause change in an organization. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/factors-may-cause-changeorganization-203.html "}, {"number": 72, "question": "Sandra is a manager at a distribution plant. Lately, her customers have been complaining about timely deliveries. Which area of the business does Sandra need to focus on to ensure on-time delivery? ", "choices": ["A. The sales force", "B. Inventory control", "C. Supply chain management", "D. Production"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Supply chain management. Supply chain management is a career area in which employees supervise the complete process of getting products into the marketplace\u2014a career field in which employees are responsible for the flow of goods from the manufacturer to the end user. Inventory control is the tracking of the amount, the kind, and the value of inventory that a business has on hand. The sales force sells the products and services but is not necessarily responsible for delivery. Production is the process of creating goods and services, but is not responsible for delivery. SOURCE: OP:477 SOURCE: NC State Pool College of Management Supply Chain Resource Cooperative. (2017, April 2). What is supply chain management (SCM)? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://scm.ncsu.edu/scm-articles/article/what-is-supply-chain-management "}, {"number": 73, "question": "Which step of the decision-making model involves identifying what you want to do? ", "choices": ["A. Gathering the information you need", "B. Establishing decision criteria", "C. Determining what you need to know", "D. Pinpointing your objective"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Pinpointing your objective. When you identify what you want to do, you are pinpointing your objective. This is the first step of the decision-making model. Establishing decision criteria involves determining what will make or break the decision for you. Determining what you need to know and gathering the information you need both come after pinpointing your objective. To figure out what you need to know and then to find that information, you first need to identify exactly what it is that you want to do. SOURCE: PD:017 SOURCE: LAP-PD-010\u2014Weigh Your Options (Decision Making in Business) "}, {"number": 74, "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of corporate governance: ", "choices": ["A. It encourages transparency.", "B. It decreases investor confidence.", "C. It creates a less definable brand.", "D. It maximizes corruption."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "It encourages transparency. Corporate governance creates a more transparent business environment, which can increase investor confidence, create a defined brand, and minimize corruption. SOURCE: PD:213 SOURCE: Management Study Guide. (2017). Corporate governance - Definition, scope, and benefits. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.managementstudyguide.com/corporategovernance.htm "}, {"number": 75, "question": "Members of a board of directors are ", "choices": ["A. required to be stockholders.", "B. elected by stockholders.", "C. a business's vendors.", "D. not able to make decisions."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Elected by stockholders. A board of directors is elected by stockholders. Board members may be stockholders, but they are not required to be. Vendors are not board members. The board of directors makes many decisions for the business. SOURCE: PD:214 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2015, December 16). Board of directors - B of D. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.investopedia.com/terms/b/boardofdirectors.asp "}, {"number": 76, "question": "Which of the following most likely led to a greater emphasis on governance structures in recent years: ", "choices": ["A. New technology in the industry", "B. Competitor saturation", "C. Stock market crash", "D. Accounting fraud"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Accounting fraud. Governance structures help balance the interests of a company's stakeholders and would most likely be impacted by internal happenings such as accounting fraud. Competitor saturation, a stock market crash, and new technology in the industry are all examples of external factors that most likely would not affect a company's governance structure. SOURCE: PD:302 SOURCE: Shaftoe, R. (2013, June 29). Reasons for corporate governance. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/reasons-corporate-governance-70176.html Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 28 "}, {"number": 77, "question": "Performances standards should be ", "choices": ["A. informally discussed.", "B. subjective.", "C. measurable.", "D. extremely challenging."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Measurable. When an organization is developing performance standards, it should ensure that those standards are measurable so that they can actually be used to evaluate performance. Performance standards should be objective rather than subjective. They also should be clearly stated in writing rather than informally discussed. Finally, performance standards should be realistic rather than extremely challenging. SOURCE: PD:256 SOURCE: U.S. Office of Personnel Management. (n.d.). Performance management: Developing performance standards. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.opm.gov/policydata-oversight/performance-management/performance-managementcycle/planning/developing-performance-standards "}, {"number": 78, "question": "Product pricing is affected by transportation costs, which are factors related to the marketing element of ", "choices": ["A. competition.", "B. promotion.", "C. place.", "D. selling."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Place. Place is the marketing element focusing on considerations in getting a selected product in the right place at the right time. An aspect of the place element is transportation. When pricing its product, a business must cover all of the costs associated with the item, including transporting it to the desired location (place). If transportation costs increase, the business may need to increase its product's price because it will cost more to get it to the customer. Transportation costs are not factors related to promotion, competition, or selling. SOURCE: PI:001 SOURCE: LAP-PI-002\u2014The Price Is Right (Nature of Pricing) "}, {"number": 79, "question": "Companies X, Y, and Z determine the selling price of widgets because these companies are the only ones who market widgets. This is an example of ", "choices": ["A. monopolistic competition.", "B. an oligopolistic market.", "C. pure competition.", "D. a true monopoly."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "An oligopolistic market. This is a market in which there are relatively few sellers, and industry leaders usually determine prices. In a monopoly, there is only one seller or provider of a good or service, and no substitutes are readily available. In a monopolistic competitive market, there are many buyers and sellers and a range of prices, rather than a single market price. In pure competition, there are a great many buyers and sellers of nearly identical products, and marketers have very little control over pricing. SOURCE: PI:002 SOURCE: LAP-PI-003\u2014Make Cents (Factors Affecting Selling Prices) "}, {"number": 80, "question": "When evaluating customers' experiences, a company should keep in mind that customers are most often influenced by their interactions with the company's ", "choices": ["A. negotiation committee.", "B. suppliers.", "C. labor union.", "D. employees."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Employees. The way that customers experience purchase transactions affects how they view the company. Good experiences often bring the customers back, while unpleasant experiences can prompt customers to purchase from the company's competitors. The ways that employees interact with customers have a major impact on the customers' experiences and their perceptions of the company. Helpful, courteous, and knowledgeable employees foster good customer experiences. Employees who are indifferent, rude, and lacking in knowledge often have a negative effect on the customers' experiences. Customers do not usually interact with the company's suppliers, labor union, or negotiation committee. SOURCE: PM:138 SOURCE: Brookins, M. (2011, September 28). Top ten ways to improve a customer's experience. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/top-ten-ways-improvecustomers-experience-25745.html "}, {"number": 81, "question": "Having a narrow product mix allows a company to ", "choices": ["A. specialize in specific product lines.", "B. mass market its products.", "C. produce less efficiently.", "D. appeal to customers with a variety of needs."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Specialize in specific product lines. A narrow product mix consists of a limited number of product lines. This means the company cannot meet a wide variety of consumer needs, but it does enable the company to specialize, to produce efficiently, to relate the products to the target market, and to concentrate on marketing the product lines. SOURCE: PM:003 SOURCE: LAP-PM-003\u2014Mix and Match (The Nature of the Product Mix) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 29 "}, {"number": 82, "question": "Ways that a business's website can provide customer-service support are by offering ", "choices": ["A. chat rooms, account numbers, and financial information.", "B. free delivery, email options, and credit authorizations.", "C. product/service updates, FAQs page, and an online help desk.", "D. online billing, sales reports, and toll-free telephone number."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Product/Service updates, FAQs page, and an online help desk. Providing around-the-clock access to information needed by customers to free up the sales staff on the floor to sell is a productive way that a business's website can provide customer service. Customers seeking post-sales support can be encouraged to access the website to locate answers, product information, etc. The alternatives are not ways that a business's website provides customer-service support. SOURCE: PM:036 SOURCE: Dun & Bradstreet. (2000-2017). Service & support. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.dnb.com/utility-pages/customer-service.html "}, {"number": 83, "question": "When a business offers services such as an information desk, child-friendly restrooms, and a lost-andfound department, it is providing customers with __________ services. ", "choices": ["A. shopping", "B. convenience", "C. community", "D. impulse"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Convenience. Customers appreciate businesses that provide services that meet their needs and are convenient. All types of businesses offer information desks, child-friendly restrooms, and a lost-and-found department. Shopping services might include gift wrapping, personal shoppers, and valet parking. Impulse is an unrelated term. Community services are activities undertaken by the store for the benefit of the community. SOURCE: PM:013 SOURCE: LAP-PM-001\u2014Customer Service Supersized (The Role of Customer Service in Positioning/Image) "}, {"number": 84, "question": "Which of the following is one of the main functions of promotion in the advertising industry: ", "choices": ["A. Marketing", "B. Persuading", "C. Branding", "D. Retailing"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Persuading. Promotion refers to the various types of communications used to inform, persuade, or remind customers of products. In the advertising industry, one of the main functions of promotion is persuading customers to buy products, change their opinions or beliefs, or participate in activities or events. Therefore, advertisements usually include headlines, photographs, and copy that are intended to be persuasive and encourage people to do what the ad suggests. For example, an ad containing a photo of a happy child playing with a particular toy might persuade parents to buy that toy for their children. Marketing is the process of planning and executing the conception, pricing, promotion, and distribution of ideas, goods, and services to create exchanges that satisfy individual and organizational objectives. Branding involves developing a business's distinctive logo, design, or identity. Retailing involves buying consumer goods or services and selling them to the ultimate consumer. SOURCE: PR:001 SOURCE: LAP-PR-002\u2014Razzle Dazzle (Nature of Promotion) "}, {"number": 85, "question": "Which of the following media could increase a business's sales by reaching people who are driving home from work: ", "choices": ["A. Email", "B. Publicity", "C. Advertising", "D. Radio"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Radio. As a type of advertising, radio can target customers at various times of the day such as when people are driving to or from work listening to their radios. Publicity is any nonpersonal presentation of ideas, goods, or services that is not paid for by the company or individual that benefits from or is harmed by it. Email should not be checked (e.g., on smartphones) while driving. This is not only dangerous\u2014it is illegal in many jurisdictions. SOURCE: PR:007 SOURCE: LAP-PR-003\u2014Ad-quipping Your Business (Types of Advertising Media) "}, {"number": 86, "question": "Mark doesn't have much money to promote his new restaurant, so he focuses on inviting a few customers in for a special dinner in hopes that they will post favorable reviews online and tell their family and friends about their great meals. Mark is using __________ marketing. ", "choices": ["A. broadcast", "B. direct mail", "C. grassroots", "D. cause"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Grassroots. Grassroots marketing involves relying on a group of customers to spread a company's marketing message. Cause marketing occurs when a company partners with a nonprofit or charity in a way that benefits both organizations. Mark is not using direct mail or broadcast marketing. SOURCE: PR:247 SOURCE: Myers, C. (2011, September 13). Definition of grassroots marketing. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/definition-grassroots-marketing-23210.html Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 30 "}, {"number": 87, "question": "Businesses often use direct advertising strategies because ", "choices": ["A. the promotional message reaches a larger group of people.", "B. they can select and reach qualified prospects.", "C. direct advertising is less expensive than other forms of promotion.", "D. it reduces the need to include other elements in the promotional mix."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "They can select and reach qualified prospects. By possessing the means to qualify potential customers, businesses can reduce waste in terms of sending promotional messages to uninterested parties. As a result, the businesses can focus their efforts on developing a customer base that is most likely to buy. Direct advertising is not necessarily less expensive than other forms of promotion. Direct advertising messages generally reach a select target audience that varies in size. Promotional mix refers to the combination of communication channels that a business uses to send its messages to consumers. Use of direct advertising strategies does not necessarily mean businesses do not need to use other promotional methods to reach customers. SOURCE: PR:089 SOURCE: Kurtz, D.L. (2013). Contemporary marketing (pp. 501-509). Mason, OH: South-Western Cengage Learning. "}, {"number": 88, "question": "The Skintastic Cosmetic Company implemented a challenging sales promotion in which its independent sales consultants could earn bonuses, prizes, and vacations. This is an example of a company using __________ as a sales incentive. ", "choices": ["A. sweepstakes", "B. push money", "C. cooperative advertising", "D. loyalty programs"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Push money. To increase market visibility, manufacturers often use incentive programs to motivate their independent sales consultants or distributors. These incentives, which are often called push money, may include cash bonuses, prizes, gift cards, or vacations. Typically, independent sales consultants must reach a certain level of sales to obtain push money. Sweepstakes involve games of chance in which customers win prizes. Manufacturers develop cooperative advertising programs to provide channel members with financial assistance to offset product advertising expenses. The purpose of loyalty or frequency programs is to build long-term customer relationships by offering incentives that encourage repeat sales. For example, a pizza chain might give customers a free pizza after they buy six pizzas of similar value. SOURCE: PR:249 SOURCE: KnowThis.com. (2017). Sales incentives or push money. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.knowthis.com/types-of-sales-promotion/sales-incentives-or-push-money "}, {"number": 89, "question": "The use of communications channels in public relations activities is an important part of ", "choices": ["A. advertising an image.", "B. marketing products.", "C. providing information.", "D. targeting customers."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Providing information. A communications channel is a path or means used to provide information to others. The various public relations activities are ways of providing information to others. For example, press conferences and press releases are ways of providing information to the media in the hopes that the media will publish or broadcast the information so it is available to the general public. However, there is no guarantee that the media will publish or broadcast the information. As a result, businesses use other techniques to market products, advertise an image, and target customers. SOURCE: PR:250 SOURCE: Crystal, G., Joseph, A., & Foster, N. (2017, August 21). What is public relations? Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.wisegeek.com/what-is-public-relations.htm "}, {"number": 90, "question": "Francine likes the auto shop where she takes her car for an oil change because it has a comfortable waiting room with good magazines. This illustrates which important characteristic of quality service providers? ", "choices": ["A. Responsiveness", "B. Reliability", "C. Tangibles", "D. Assurance"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Tangibles. A comfortable waiting room with good magazines is an example of a service provider having quality tangibles\u2014a characteristic that customers are looking for. Reliability means that the service is consistently well-performed. Responsiveness means that the service provider provides the service willingly and promptly. Assurance means that the customer finds the service provider to be knowledgeable and trustworthy. SOURCE: QM:001 SOURCE: LAP-QM-001\u2014Keep It Quality (Nature of Quality Management) "}, {"number": 91, "question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding the relationship between risk and business objectives: ", "choices": ["A. Risks help businesses determine objectives.", "B. Objectives should never be modified because of risk.", "C. Effective business objectives are not risky.", "D. The more objectives a business has, the less risk it faces."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Risks help businesses determine objectives. When businesses are determining their objectives, they must consider risks related to these objectives and ensure that these risks are manageable. Objectives should be modified because of risk. If a new risk threatens a business objective, it should be changed to accommodate that risk. Business objectives almost always have at least some risk associated with them. Finally, the number of objectives is not necessarily related to the amount of risk. SOURCE: RM:044 SOURCE: Marks, N. (2012, January 20). The inter-relationships of risk, objectives, strategy and performance. Retrieved September 18, 2017, from https://normanmarks.wordpress.com/2012/01/20/risk-objectives-strategy-and-performance Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 31 "}, {"number": 92, "question": "Tyrese and his team are creating a list of their company's critical enterprise-wide risks. They are compiling ", "choices": ["A. a risk control.", "B. a risk assessment.", "C. enterprise risk management.", "D. a risk inventory."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "A risk inventory. A risk inventory is a listing of an organization's entire critical enterprise-wide risks. A risk assessment is a tool used in risk management. Enterprise risk management allows a company to plan, organize, lead, and control the risk in every level of an organization. A risk control is a tactic to mitigate a perceived risk. SOURCE: RM:062 SOURCE: Patterson, T. (2015, September). The use of information technology in risk management. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.aicpa.org/interestareas/frc/assuranceadvisoryservices/downloadabledocuments/a sec_whitepapers/risk_technology.pdf "}, {"number": 93, "question": "Which of the following situations is most likely to result in long-term, increased sales for a business: ", "choices": ["A. Raising the price of its current products", "B. Constantly providing new choices for consumers", "C. Lowering the price of its current products", "D. Eliminating a slow-selling product line"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Constantly providing new choices for consumers. There is much competition between businesses, which leads to increased competition to produce better products. Businesses need to develop new or improved products in order to make more sales than their competitors. A company that raises or lowers the prices of existing products may make temporary sales gains, but only a company that provides choices based on the needs of its consumers will enjoy a long-term sales increase. Elimination of a slow-selling product line may not increase sales for a business. SOURCE: SE:017 SOURCE: LAP-SE-117\u2014Sell Away (The Nature and Scope of Selling) "}, {"number": 94, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a company objective that might be developed by top management: ", "choices": ["A. To improve the collection process", "B. To maintain or increase market share", "C. To maintain the billing cycle", "D. To hold weekly sales meetings"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "To maintain or increase market share. This is an overall objective for the entire company that would be set by top management. Deciding to hold weekly sales meetings, do a better job of collecting past-due bills, or to keep the billing up-to-date are specific objectives that might be set by department managers. SOURCE: SM:008 SOURCE: Root, G.N. (2011, September 17). 10 most important business objectives. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/10-important-business-objectives23686.html "}, {"number": 95, "question": "A business should consider the impact that changes in the environment will have on the business's marketing mix because ", "choices": ["A. most businesses want to be reactive.", "B. the business can change its marketing mix.", "C. the marketing mix is affected by technology.", "D. government regulations can increase costs."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "The business can change its marketing mix. While the business cannot control the external factors in the environment that affect the business, the business can change its marketing mix (price, place, product, promotion) to reflect any shifts in the environment. That is why most businesses prefer to be proactive by planning ways to cope with expected changes. Government regulations can increase the costs of doing business, and the marketing mix may be affected by technology, but those are not reasons the business should consider the impact of changes on the marketing mix. SOURCE: SM:011 SOURCE: Riley, J. (2015). External environment: Introduction (GCSE). Retrieved September 19, 2017, from https://www.tutor2u.net/business/reference/external-environment-introduction "}, {"number": 96, "question": "Which component of the business plan requires considerable time and external research? ", "choices": ["A. Market analysis", "B. Executive summary", "C. Strategy and implementation", "D. Appendices"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Market analysis. The market analysis requires considerable time and external research. The executive summary, strategy and implementation section, and appendices may require some time to put together, but they do not necessarily require external research. SOURCE: SM:013 SOURCE: LAP-SM-013\u2014Plan for Success (Creating a Business Plan) Test 1167 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 32 "}, {"number": 97, "question": "What company has the highest sales-to-receivables ratio based on the following information: Company A has sales of $250,000 and accounts receivable of $20,000; Company B has sales of $275,000 and accounts receivable of $25,000; Company C has sales of $300,000 and accounts receivable of $30,000; and Company D has sales of $290,000 and accounts receivable of $32,000. ", "choices": ["A. Company A", "B. Company B", "C. Company C", "D. Company D"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Company A. Businesses often compare their sales-to-receivables ratios with industry standards in order to determine if they are collecting cash as quickly as others. If businesses find that they have low salesto-receivables ratios, they might make adjustments to their collection procedures in order to receive payment in a more timely manner. To calculate Company A's sales-to-receivables ratio, divide sales by accounts receivable ($250,000 \u00f7 $20,000 = 12.5). This figure indicates that receivables turn over more than 12 times a year which means there is a shorter time between making the sale and collecting the cash. SOURCE: SM:005 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2017, August 10). Receivables turnover ratio. Retrieved September 19, 2017, from http://www.investopedia.com/terms/r/receivableturnoverratio.asp "}, {"number": 98, "question": "Why is it important to track the performance of a business plan? ", "choices": ["A. To establish an operating strategy", "B. To find out if products are selling", "C. To determine its proposed mission", "D. To provide investment information"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "To find out if products are selling. A business plan is a proposal of how a business intends to operate to achieve its objective. It is important to track the performance of a business plan to determine if the objective of the business is being met. A main objective for most businesses is to sell products. By tracking the performance of the strategies outlined in the business plan, a business is able to find out if the strategies it is using to sell are effective. If the business is not satisfied with the level of sales, it might develop different strategies. Developing a business plan involves establishing an operating strategy and determining the proposed mission of the company. Businesses often use a business plan to provide investment information to potential investors. SOURCE: SM:006 SOURCE: Berry, T. (2017, May 12). How to use your business plan to track your progress and exceed your goals. Retrieved September 20, 2017, from http://articles.bplans.com/how-to-use-yourbusiness-plan-to-track-your-progress-and-exceed-your-goals/ "}, {"number": 99, "question": "For successful innovation to occur, employees must be willing to __________ while developing ideas. ", "choices": ["A. learn", "B. teach", "C. avoid results", "D. work alone"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Learn. For successful innovation to occur, employees must be willing to learn while developing ideas. The development process involves learning and accepting change. Employees do not necessarily have to teach while developing ideas. They should review their results and learn from them, not avoid them. Innovation does not necessarily occur when employees work alone; it may happen when employees are working together. SOURCE: SM:094 SOURCE: Muse, C., & Smith, J. (n.d.) Cultivating innovation in the workplace. Retrieved September 20, 2017, from http://managementhelp.org/innovation/ "}, {"number": 100, "question": "If a company wants to ensure that changes are implemented in the best possible way and that those changes will lead to long-term benefits, it should use the __________ approach. ", "choices": ["A. change avoidance", "B. problem solving", "C. change management", "D. solution finding"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Change management. The change management approach ensures that changes are implemented in the best possible way and that those changes will lead to long-term benefits. Change management is not referred to as problem solving, change avoidance, or solution finding. SOURCE: SM:095 SOURCE: MindTools. (1996-2017) Change management: Making organization change happen effectively. Retrieved September 20, 2017, from https://www.mindtools.com/pages/article/newPPM_87.ht"}], "1197-ENT-STATE": [{"number": 1, "question": "An employer may be liable for an employee's tort when the employee's actions occur ", "choices": ["A. within the scope of his/her employment.", "B. under emotional stress.", "C. within normal operating hours.", "D. without the employer's knowledge."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Within the scope of his/her employment. Under the doctrine of respondeat superior, an employer may be held responsible for an employee's tort if the employee's wrongful or harmful actions are related to his/her job. For example, if an employee causes an accident while driving the company's truck to deliver an order, the company can be held liable for damages and injuries resulting from the accident. Although the employer may not know about the accident at the time that it occurred, the employer is likely to be held liable for the accident because the employee was acting on the employer's behalf. Wrongful actions related to work may occur during or after normal working hours. Although the employee's wrongful actions may be related to his/her emotional stress, the employer can still be held liable for the tort as long as the action is related to the employee's job responsibilities. SOURCE: BL:069 SOURCE: Legal Information Institute. (2017, October 16). Respondeat superior. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.law.cornell.edu/wex/respondeat_superior "}, {"number": 2, "question": "In a contract, what one party gives or receives in exchange for something else is an example of ", "choices": ["A. acceptance.", "B. agreement.", "C. compensation.", "D. consideration."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Consideration. In a contract, consideration is what one party gives or receives in exchange for something else. In order for a contract to be legally binding, something of value must be exchanged. For example, one party might sell a product to another party and receive monetary payment. Both the product and the monetary payment have value. What one party gives or receives in exchange for something else is not an example of agreement, compensation, or acceptance. SOURCE: BL:002 SOURCE: Stim, R. (2015, April 23). Consideration: Every contract needs it. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from http://www.nolo.com/legal-encyclopedia/consideration-every-contract-needs33361.html "}, {"number": 3, "question": "What do federal regulations concerning workplace issues require businesses to provide to qualified individuals with disabilities? ", "choices": ["A. Compensation packages", "B. Preferential treatment", "C. Reasonable accommodations", "D. Psychological counseling"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Reasonable accommodations. Reasonable accommodations involve providing some type of assistance to qualified employees who have limitations in order for them to do their jobs. Federal regulations require businesses to provide reasonable accommodations so that qualified employees with disabilities have the opportunity to obtain or keep their jobs. Providing reasonable accommodations does not mean changing the way that a company does business, but it does involve making reasonable concessions such as a simple modification of equipment. Federal regulations do not require businesses to provide preferential treatment or psychological counseling to qualified individuals with disabilities. Businesses provide compensation packages to all employees based on the type of work they do, their qualifications, their education, their seniority, etc. SOURCE: BL:008 SOURCE: Repa, B.K. (2015, August 14). Your right to a reasonable accommodation under the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.nolo.com/legal-encyclopedia/free-books/employee-rights-book/chapter7-8.html "}, {"number": 4, "question": "Which of the following forms of business ownership has the most potential for financial power: ", "choices": ["A. Sole proprietorship", "B. General partnership", "C. Corporation", "D. Limited liability partnership"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Corporation. Because a public corporation has the ability to sell millions of shares of stock to anyone who can afford to purchase it, the corporate structure has the most financial power. In addition, financial institutions tend to lend higher amounts of money to corporations because the lenders view them as a lower risk than other forms of business ownership. Sole proprietorships, general partnerships, and limited liability partnerships do not generally have the financial resources that are available to corporations. SOURCE: BL:006 SOURCE: LAP-BL-006\u2014Taking Care of Business (Selecting Forms of Business Ownership) "}, {"number": 5, "question": "The costs of promoting products are often ", "choices": ["A. avoidable in certain channels.", "B. shared by channel members.", "C. very inexpensive, especially for new products.", "D. paid for entirely by one channel member."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Shared by channel members. The costs of promoting products are often shared by channel members instead of being paid for entirely by one channel member. All products need to be promoted. Promotion costs are unavoidable and are often expensive, especially for new products. SOURCE: CM:001 SOURCE: LAP-CM-002\u2014Chart Your Channels (Channel Management) Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 14 "}, {"number": 6, "question": "The most likely channel of distribution to be used by a manufacturer of machine parts is ", "choices": ["A. producer to industrial distributor to user.", "B. manufacturer to industrial user to retailer.", "C. producer to distribution (transfer) company.", "D. industrial warehouse to agent to user."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Producer to industrial distributor to user. Industrial distributors function in much the same way as wholesalers for consumer goods. They buy large quantities of goods and raw materials from producers and sell small quantities to industrial users. Chemicals and machine parts often move through this channel. SOURCE: CM:003 SOURCE: LAP-CM-003\u2014Channel It (Channels of Distribution) "}, {"number": 7, "question": "Businesses regularly meet with channel members to discuss problems and improve performance in order to develop ", "choices": ["A. routine buying procedures.", "B. cost-effective inventories.", "C. transportation systems.", "D. long-term partnerships."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Long-term partnerships. Most businesses want to develop long-term partnerships with channel members because it is more cost effective to maintain a relationship with an existing member than to locate new channel members. To accomplish this, businesses often meet regularly with channel members to discuss problems and evaluate performance. This gives both the business and the channel members an opportunity to discuss problems and decide on a mutually satisfactory solution. By working together, the business and the channel members can improve performance and develop a long-term partnership. Businesses and channel members do not meet regularly to develop transportation systems, costeffective inventories, or routine buying procedures. SOURCE: CM:011 SOURCE: Logic Bay. (2015, November 17). How to build stronger relationships with your current channel partners. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.logicbay.com/blog/howto-build-stronger-relationships-with-your-current-channel-partners "}, {"number": 8, "question": "Southwest Airlines expects its employees to reinforce the company's brand promise\u2014high-quality customer service\u2014at all times. Which of the following is the most significant aspect of the brand promise for all Southwest employees to remember? ", "choices": ["A. Profit maximization", "B. Consistent follow-through", "C. Ongoing promotion", "D. Long-term planning"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Consistent follow-through. A brand promise is a company's agreement, spoken or unspoken, with customers that it will meet their expectations and deliver on its brand characteristics and values. A company must follow through by performing certain actions in consistent ways to fulfill that promise. Both long- and short-term planning can help the company develop strategies to carry out the brand promise; however, unless the strategies are carried out consistently, the planning efforts are useless. Ongoing promotion helps maintain brand awareness, but it does not fulfill the company's commitment to the customer through product quality, service, etc. The company's profits involve setting internal goals rather than carrying out promises made to customers. SOURCE: CR:001 SOURCE: LAP-CR-006\u2014Share the Promise (Identifying Brand Promise) "}, {"number": 9, "question": "In a private enterprise economic system, the incentive for producing goods and services is ", "choices": ["A. competition.", "B. advertising.", "C. marketing.", "D. profit."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Profit. Profit is the monetary reward a business owner receives for taking the risk involved in investing in a business. It is the driving force behind the private enterprise system. Advertising is any paid form of nonpersonal presentation of ideas, goods, or services. Marketing is the process of planning and executing the pricing, promotion, and distribution of ideas, goods, and services to create exchanges that satisfy individual and organizational objectives. Competition is the rivalry between two or more businesses to attract scarce customer dollars. SOURCE: EC:009 SOURCE: LAP-EC-015\u2014People Power (The Private Enterprise System) "}, {"number": 10, "question": "Two businesses that are involved in used-auto sales are considered to be ", "choices": ["A. direct competitors.", "B. monopolies.", "C. partnerships.", "D. unfair competitors."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Direct competitors. Direct competitors are businesses that offer similar types of goods or services. They compete with each other for customers, but this is not necessarily unfair. Monopolies occur when one business controls the products being offered, and there is no substitute product readily available. Partnerships occur when two or more people own one business. SOURCE: EC:012 SOURCE: LAP-EC-008\u2014Ready, Set, Compete! (Competition) Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 15 "}, {"number": 11, "question": "The primary purpose of most government regulation of consumer products is to ", "choices": ["A. protect consumers.", "B. increase prices.", "C. protect producers.", "D. increase production."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Protect consumers. Government has passed many laws for the sole purpose of protecting consumers from unsafe products. As new products grow in sophistication and complexity, the need for government regulation increases. Consumers need information about product contents, procedures for use and care, and any additional information that can protect their welfare. Such government action is not intended to increase prices or production. In some cases, producers are also protected when they are prevented from marketing inferior or unsafe products, but that is a side effect rather than a primary purpose of consumer-product laws. SOURCE: EC:008 SOURCE: LAP-EC-016\u2014Regulate and Protect (Government and Business) "}, {"number": 12, "question": "Which of the following is the ultimate goal of selling ideas to others: ", "choices": ["A. Developing your leadership and presentation skills", "B. Gaining enthusiasm and engagement from teammates", "C. Receiving recognition for your idea from your team", "D. Obtaining a promotion or a raise because of your idea"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Gaining enthusiasm and engagement from teammates. The ultimate goal of idea selling is to gain the enthusiasm and engagement of your teammates. Obtaining a promotion or a raise, receiving recognition, and developing your leadership skills are potential benefits of successfully selling an idea\u2014but none is the ultimate goal of idea selling. SOURCE: EI:108 SOURCE: LAP-EI-108\u2014Do They Buy It? (\"Selling\" Ideas to Others) "}, {"number": 13, "question": "Pedro wants to negotiate with his supervisor to gain more responsibilities at work. Before approaching his supervisor, Pedro needs to determine the supervisor's position and ", "choices": ["A. standards.", "B. skills.", "C. interests.", "D. procedures."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Interests. To have a successful negotiation, it\u2019s important for Pedro to focus on interests. Interests are the things that each party wants or needs. For Pedro to gain more responsibilities, he needs to consider his supervisor\u2019s interests as well as his own. Skill is the ability to perform a task through knowledge, training, and practice. When negotiating, one person may not necessarily know the other person\u2019s skills. Standards are specifications or statements that are used as a basis for comparing or judging goods or services. A procedure is the step-by-step process someone follows when performing a specific task. SOURCE: EI:062 SOURCE: LAP-EI-062\u2014Make It a Win-Win (Negotiation in Business) "}, {"number": 14, "question": "Team building within an organization often includes ", "choices": ["A. staffing.", "B. recruiting.", "C. training.", "D. interviewing."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Training. Team building within an organization often includes training because all members of the team may not have the same knowledge or skills. If the team is expected to address a certain problem or issue, it may be necessary to provide training so all members will understand. To be effective, the team must be able to work on the same level, which often means some basic training will be necessary. Team building within an organization usually does not include recruiting, staffing, or interviewing. SOURCE: EI:044 SOURCE: Morrison, K. (2014, October 8). Encourage team building with training sessions. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.getadministrate.com/blog/encourage-team-buildingwith-training-sessions/ "}, {"number": 15, "question": "To become more adaptable, you must see change as a(n) __________ experience. ", "choices": ["A. convenient", "B. unwelcome", "C. learning", "D. comfortable"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Learning. If you want to be a more adaptable person, you have to alter the way you look at change. Adaptable people see changes as opportunities to grow and learn new skills. People who refuse to adapt see change as unwelcome. Change is necessary, but it isn't always convenient. Being adaptable requires getting out of your comfort zone. SOURCE: EI:006 SOURCE: LAP-EI-023\u2014Go With the Flow (Demonstrating Adaptability) "}, {"number": 16, "question": "Collette wants to fill out at least five job applications this week. What standard has she set for her success? ", "choices": ["A. Past performance", "B. An objective measure", "C. Outperforming others", "D. Improvement"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "An objective measure. Collette has set an objective measure for her success\u2014filling out five job applications this week. If she fills out less than five, she will not consider her goal to have been achieved. In this case, she is not basing her success standard on past performance, improvement, or outperforming others. SOURCE: EI:027 SOURCE: LAP-EI-027\u2014High Hopes (Developing an Achievement Orientation) Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 16 "}, {"number": 17, "question": "A CEO wants to create a company culture that values learning and cooperation. The CEO should ", "choices": ["A. use a functional organizational structure.", "B. replace current employees with friends.", "C. set high sales quotas to motivate employees.", "D. share best practices with the staff."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Share best practices with the staff. Sharing best practices means maintaining and disseminating the actions and strategies that have been most successful for an organization. It helps organizations grow, and it encourages employees to value learning and cooperate with one another to achieve results. Replacing current employees with friends, setting high sales quotas, and using a functional organizational structure would not necessarily help the CEO create a company culture that values learning and cooperation. SOURCE: EI:115 SOURCE: Memari, E. (2018, May 18). 9 benefits of sharing best practices in an organization. Retrieved November 23, 2018, from https://elearningindustry.com/sharing-best-practices-organization9-benefits "}, {"number": 18, "question": "What is necessary for goods and services to exist? ", "choices": ["A. Entrepreneurial discovery", "B. Product standards", "C. Demographic changes", "D. Raw materials"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Entrepreneurial discovery. A good or service begins with an idea. Entrepreneurial discovery is a process used to generate an idea and bring it to fruition. The entrepreneurial discovery process involves detecting and matching product and market opportunities with one another in a manner that satisfies the market and the business. Product standards are the criteria for determining a product's ability to meet specified guidelines or requirements. Raw materials are items in their natural state or condition. Demographic changes are often factors that spark ideas and lead to entrepreneurial discovery. SOURCE: EN:001 SOURCE: Manev, I. (2012, January 6). Discovering the entrepreneurial opportunity. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://bangordailynews.com/2012/01/06/business/deans-ofbusiness/discovering-the-entrepreneurial-opportunity/ "}, {"number": 19, "question": "Landon started a furniture manufacturing company several years ago and is considering expanding his product line to attract new customers. Landon is currently evaluating the company's existing resources to determine ways that he can apply his current capabilities to new product opportunities. What type of analysis is Landon conducting? ", "choices": ["A. Inside-out", "B. External-focus", "C. Competitive", "D. Cultural"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Inside-out. An inside-out analysis involves looking at internal abilities and resources to identify venture and product opportunities. A new entrepreneur may first look at his/her personal abilities and resources to determine what type of business might be best for him/her. Landon may have started a furniture business because he was a good carpenter. Today, Landon's business is larger and has more resources, so he may determine that he has the capabilities within his business to add interior decorating or design services. Another approach to determining venture and product opportunities is by conducting an outside-in analysis. In this situation, the entrepreneur looks at external factors, such as unmet market needs, to identify opportunities. Competition and culture are other external considerations that entrepreneurs consider when identifying venture and product opportunities. SOURCE: EN:004 SOURCE: Lagerstedt, E. (2014, August 15). Business strategy: Are you inside-out or outside-in? Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://knowledge.insead.edu/blog/inseadblog/business-strategy-are-you-inside-out-or-outside-in-3515 "}, {"number": 20, "question": "At the end of a feasibility study, owners/managers may decide to ", "choices": ["A. postpone the venture until a later time.", "B. pass the results along to competitors.", "C. run the study a second time.", "D. switch industries."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Postpone the venture until a later time. At the end of a feasibility study, owners/managers may decide to proceed with the venture, scrap the idea, or possibly postpone it until a later or more advantageous time. Feasibility studies are time-consuming and expensive\u2014a business would not want to share the information with competitors. There should be no need to run the study a second time (if it's been conducted correctly) or to switch industries. SOURCE: EN:038 SOURCE: LAP-EN-038\u2014Explore the Possibilities (Conducting Feasibility Studies) Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 17 "}, {"number": 21, "question": "When planning for her new business, Janine allocates 2% of the company's estimated annual sales to web and newspaper advertising. Janine is developing a ", "choices": ["A. promotional budget.", "B. sales report.", "C. competitive analysis.", "D. publicity plan."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Promotional budget. Promotion is important to new venture owners because they need to let the target audience know that the business has goods and services available for purchase. A promotional budget is the amount of money a business plans to spend on promoting its goods and services during a certain time. Businesses consider historical data and estimated sales to determine how much to spend on promotion. A sales report provides information about a firm's sales volume. A competitive analysis is an evaluation of a competitor's activities. Publicity is any nonpersonal presentation of ideas, goods, or services that is not paid for by the company or individual that benefits or is harmed by it. SOURCE: EN:008 SOURCE: Mintz, L. (2015, March 11). How to determine the perfect marketing budget for your company. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/243790 "}, {"number": 22, "question": "Costs of sales for a new manufacturing venture typically include ", "choices": ["A. Internet access, attorney fees, and sales lead lists.", "B. trade show attendance, raw materials, and equipment.", "C. trade show attendance, product inventory, and Internet access.", "D. raw materials, equipment, and product inventory."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Raw materials, equipment, and product inventory. Costs of sales for a new manufacturing venture typically include raw materials, equipment, product inventory, warehousing, shipping, and packaging. Trade show attendance and sales lead lists fall in the sales and marketing costs category. Attorney fees are a professional expense. Internet access is a technology cost. SOURCE: EN:009 SOURCE: Murray, J. (2018, April 18). Cost of goods sold (cost of sales). Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.thebalancesmb.com/cost-of-goods-sold-398161 "}, {"number": 23, "question": "A business should seek legal protection for its intellectual property to discourage ", "choices": ["A. the development of licensed and artistic works.", "B. the competition from developing new products.", "C. individuals from filing unnecessary lawsuits.", "D. others from using it without permission."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Others from using it without permission. Intangible business assets resulting from thinking processes are called intellectual property. Inventions, written and artistic works, logos, brand names, and trade characters are examples of intellectual property. The business can discourage others from using the intellectual property without its permission by obtaining legal protection from the government. Depending on the type of intellectual property the business seeks to protect, the government can issue a copyright, patent, or trademark. If other businesses or individuals use the legally protected materials without the business's permission, the business has a better chance of winning a lawsuit, if it chooses to sue the unauthorized user. Legal protection for intellectual property does not discourage the competition from developing new products, individuals from filing unnecessary lawsuits, or the development of licensed and artistic works. SOURCE: EN:013 SOURCE: UpCounsel. (2018). Intellectual property protection. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.upcounsel.com/intellectual-property-protection "}, {"number": 24, "question": "Other than money, an entrepreneur might select a private investor to finance a business venture because the investor has ", "choices": ["A. a proven track record for business failure.", "B. expertise that the entrepreneur lacks.", "C. a desire to risk personal integrity.", "D. indecisive personality traits."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Expertise that the entrepreneur lacks. A private investor (angel investor) is a person with personal wealth who looks for opportunities to provide money for business startups. Often, a private investor is a successful entrepreneur who invests money in the businesses in which s/he has expertise. This is beneficial to a new entrepreneur who may not have experience in the industry because the investor can provide information that may increase the startup's chance for success. The entrepreneur would probably not seek advice from a person who has failed more than s/he has succeeded in the business world. Most honest people do not go out of their way to risk their integrity. If the investor is indecisive, s/he may change his/her mind about a course of action, such as financing the entrepreneur's startup. SOURCE: EN:016 SOURCE: Intrepid Private Capital Group. (2014, October 13). The pros and cons of angel investors. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.intrepidexecutivegroup.com/blog/the-prosand-cons-of-angel-investors/ Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 18 "}, {"number": 25, "question": "What is the most important factor that Jillian should consider when she selects the photocopier for her new company? ", "choices": ["A. Unit appearance", "B. Taxation", "C. Usage", "D. Business location"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Usage. A capital resource is an asset, or something of value that a firm uses on an ongoing basis to meet its objectives. When Jillian selects the photocopier (the capital resource) for the business, she must determine how it will be used. For example, if she is using it to print high-quality graphics, she might need a photocopier that prints in color. Or, if there are several people in the workplace that will be using it a lot, she may want a heavy-duty, reliable photocopier that has collating options. Taxation, unit appearance, and business location are not usually primary factors when selecting a photocopier. SOURCE: EN:019 SOURCE: Kabbage. (2017, May 27). 7 things to consider before buying equipment for your small business. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.kabbage.com/blog/7-things-toconsider-before-buying-equipment-for-your-small-business/ "}, {"number": 26, "question": "Sally wants to incorporate her company and contracts a law firm to handle the legal aspects of the process. This is an example of ", "choices": ["A. staffing.", "B. exporting.", "C. outsourcing.", "D. designating."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Outsourcing. Outsourcing is acquiring assistance from outside organizations or consultants to obtain goods and services to perform primary business activities. Forming a corporation is complex, so it is important to make sure that the appropriate legal forms are correct. If the business does not complete the legal activities correctly, the government may fine the corporation. A knowledgeable attorney ensures that the business follows the proper procedures and legal forms are accurate. Exporting, staffing, and designating do not describe the process of contracting a law firm to handle a legal issue. SOURCE: EN:022 SOURCE: Jackson, N.M. (2017, February 14). Build a better business with outsourcing. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/204652 "}, {"number": 27, "question": "Jason is evaluating a venture opportunity that involves acquiring a large sum of funding from a lending institution, which poses a(n) __________ risk. ", "choices": ["A. low professional", "B. insignificant financial", "C. moderate professional", "D. high financial"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "High financial. Risk is the chance of failure or loss. There are many types of risks that business owners face including social, career (professional), psychic, and financial risks. The amount of risk that a business owner takes varies, but financial risk is the type of risk that is the easiest to measure. Because Jason is borrowing a large sum of money that he must repay, he is taking a high financial risk. There is not enough information about Jason to determine the amount of professional risk he is taking. SOURCE: EN:024 SOURCE: Zwilling, M. (2012, March 25). Ten high risk drivers every entrepreneur faces. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.businessinsider.com/ten-high-risk-drivers-everyentrepreneur-faces-2012-4 "}, {"number": 28, "question": "Which of the following terms best describes the overall procedures that guide a small business's activities by standardizing the way the business functions: ", "choices": ["A. Credit", "B. Operating", "C. Safety", "D. Hiring"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Operating. Operating procedures are the step-by-step processes that employees follow when they perform specific work-related tasks. By developing and implementing operating procedures, managers or owners do not need to spend time answering routine questions and making routine decisions. Operating procedures provide employees with guidelines for performing their work, which can increase productivity and efficiency. Credit, safety, and hiring are types of operating procedures. SOURCE: EN:026 SOURCE: Rush, M. (2016, October 26). Standard operating procedures for a business. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/standard-operating-proceduresbusiness-3228.html "}, {"number": 29, "question": "A small-business owner who uses the brainstorming technique to find solutions to difficult situations is trying to ", "choices": ["A. intentionally prevent conflict.", "B. assess long-term budgets.", "C. plan contract negotiations.", "D. creatively solve problems."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Creatively solve problems. Creative problem solving is the process of finding solutions to issues or obstacles (problems) by generating unique ideas or approaches. Budgets, contract negotiations, and conflict are issues that might require a business owner to use creative problem solving. SOURCE: EN:029 SOURCE: Mind Tools Content Team. (2018, October 24). Brainstorming. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.mindtools.com/brainstm.html Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 19 "}, {"number": 30, "question": "Which of the following is a personal factor that entrepreneurs should consider when developing their exit strategies, or plans to leave their businesses: ", "choices": ["A. Lifestyle changes", "B. Sales forecasts", "C. Interest rates", "D. Industry standards"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Lifestyle changes. Entrepreneurs often leave their startup ventures after they feel that they have reached their goals for the venture or are ready to start another business. It's important to plan exit strategies, so that the venture can continue to grow after the entrepreneur leaves, if that is what the entrepreneur wants. Part of the planning process is anticipating lifestyle changes. For example, an entrepreneur may retire, and find that s/he would rather be working instead of golfing or boating all day\u2014this is a lifestyle change. By anticipating lifestyle changes, the entrepreneur will be better prepared to accept or adapt to the changes when s/he exits the business. Sales forecasts, interest rates, and industry standards are examples of external factors rather than personal factors that entrepreneurs consider when developing exit strategies. SOURCE: EN:037 SOURCE: Business Filings. (2012, May 26). Consider internal and external factors when timing sale of business. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.bizfilings.com/toolkit/researchtopics/running-your-business/exit-strategies/consider-internal-and-external-factors-whentiming-sale-of-business "}, {"number": 31, "question": "In which of the following situations is a business paying more for insurance than it should: ", "choices": ["A. Premium is $1,000 a year for liability coverage of $100,000.", "B. Property is essential to the operation of the business.", "C. Replacement cost is more than purchase price of property.", "D. Premium is $500 a year on property valued at $2,000."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Premium is $500 a year on property valued at $2,000. When businesses obtain insurance coverage, they try to find insurance that best meets their needs at a reasonable price. In order to do this, businesses need to consider the value of the property they are insuring. If property has a low value, it may be more economical to pay to replace it than to pay high yearly premiums. For example, paying $500 a year to insure property that is worth $2,000 is a waste of money because only a few years of premiums would pay for a replacement. Most businesses insure property that is essential to the operation of the business and property that increases in value, because replacement is often expensive. A yearly premium of $1,000 for liability coverage of $100,000 is inexpensive. SOURCE: FI:082 SOURCE: Business Filings. (2012, May 24). How much property and liability insurance is enough for your business? Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.bizfilings.com/toolkit/research-topics/office-hr/how-much-property-and-liabilityinsurance-is-enough-for-your-business "}, {"number": 32, "question": "What documents will you access to determine cash receipts from customers when preparing cash flow statements? ", "choices": ["A. Income statement and accounts receivable", "B. Balance sheet and accounts receivable", "C. Income statement and accounts payable", "D. Balance sheet and accounts payable"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Income statement and accounts receivable. To determine cash receipts from customers, you will need to identify the net sales amount on the income statement, add in the beginning balance in accounts receivable, and subtract the ending balance in accounts receivable. The balance sheet shows a business's assets, liabilities, and owner's equity. Accounts payable would be used to determine cash payments. SOURCE: FI:092 SOURCE: Doran, Y. (n.d.). How to prepare a cash flow statement. Retrieved November 29, 2018, from http://www.ehow.com/how_4452440_prepare-cash-flow-statement.html "}, {"number": 33, "question": "Which of the following is an example of how managerial accounting is used as a measurement of performance: ", "choices": ["A. Estimating the benefits and costs of different business opportunities", "B. Evaluating whether company goals are realistic", "C. Comparing the actual results of operations to budgeted figures", "D. Planning how much to sell to achieve profits"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Comparing the actual results of operations to budgeted figures. Managerial accounting helps managers plan, make decisions, evaluate goals, and measure performance. Managerial accounting allows managers to measure business performance by comparing the actual results of operations to budgeted figures. Evaluating company goals and estimating the benefits and costs of business opportunities are decision-making activities. Planning how much to sell to achieve profits is a planning activity. SOURCE: FI:657 SOURCE: Accounting Explained. (2011-2013). Managerial accounting. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from http://accountingexplained.com/managerial/introduction/ Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 20 "}, {"number": 34, "question": "Why would a business owner consider developing a relationship with a virtual bank? ", "choices": ["A. It might offer lower rates on loans.", "B. It is located in the same community.", "C. It has convenient daytime hours.", "D. It is not controlled by regulations."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "It might offer lower rates on loans. Virtual banks operate by way of the Internet rather than in physical locations. As a result, they often have lower operating expenses because they do not need to pay for a facility or hire as many employees. Consequently, they may be able to pass on the savings in the form of offering lower rates for their services, such as loans, which is an advantage to a business. Virtual banks are available at all times, rather than just during the day, because they operate by way of the Internet. The bank may or may not be located in the same community; however, the banking services are available only online. A virtual bank is regulated the same as other banks. SOURCE: FI:039 SOURCE: Beers, B. (2018, June 26). The pros and cons of internet banks. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/articles/pf/11/benefits-and-drawbacks-of-internetbanks.asp "}, {"number": 35, "question": "A risk that the owners of new businesses often encounter when obtaining credit from a financial institution is the requirement that they ", "choices": ["A. give personal guarantees.", "B. pay processing fees.", "C. open savings accounts.", "D. accept high interest rates."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Give personal guarantees. Often the owners of new businesses are required to personally guarantee any loans or credit arrangements. This means that the owners agree to be personally responsible for the amount of the loan or credit. In the event that the business is unable to repay the loan, the owners must pay. The risk to the owners is that their personal assets will be taken to cover any losses if the business fails or encounters any difficulty in repaying the loan. Paying the processing fees is a routine part of obtaining business credit. New business owners can negotiate the interest rates and do not necessarily need to pay high rates. New business owners usually are not required to open savings accounts in order to obtain credit. SOURCE: FI:041 SOURCE: Pritchard, J. (2018, November 7). Personal guarantees help you get approved. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.thebalance.com/personal-guarantee-basics-315207 "}, {"number": 36, "question": "Lina applied for a loan at her local bank to start a new bakery, but her application was denied. She has a strong credit history, owns real estate, and has a significant amount of cash in her bank account. Based on this information, her loan was most likely denied because ", "choices": ["A. she did not provide strong references.", "B. she did not network with the bank employees.", "C. she does not have collateral.", "D. she has not repaid her debts in a timely manner."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "She did not provide strong references. One of the most important aspects of a loan application is the applicant's character. This includes having a good reputation and strong references to vouch for your ability to pay back your loans. Lina has a strong credit history and significant cash flow, so there is no indication that she has weak capital or that she has not repaid her debts in a timely manner. Finally, networking with bank employees is not necessarily an important aspect of a loan application. SOURCE: FI:034 SOURCE: Carabelli, C. (2017, November 11). What do banks look at for loans? Retrieved November 23, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/banks-look-loans-42003.html "}, {"number": 37, "question": "An established company has achieved a steady, positive cash flow. Which of the following types of funding is it most likely to rely on for unexpected expenses: ", "choices": ["A. The company's capital structure", "B. Collateral", "C. Venture capital", "D. A business line of credit"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "A business line of credit. An established company with a positive cash flow is most likely to rely on a business line of credit for any unexpected expenses. Many businesses maintain a business line of credit as a flexible funding tool to pay for unanticipated business expenses. A company with a positive cash flow has little need to use collateral or venture capital for funding. Collateral refers to property that a borrower offers to a lender to secure a loan. Venture capital refers to financing that investors provide to startup companies and small businesses that have long-term growth potential. Capital structure refers to a company's mix of financing, usually a combination of debt and equity. SOURCE: FI:339 SOURCE: Vitez, O. (2017, September 26). What are the purposes of business finance? Retrieved November 20, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/list-6787756-purposes-business-finance-.html "}, {"number": 38, "question": "When making an economic decision, comparing the costs of an action to the benefits received is called ", "choices": ["A. rational choice.", "B. upside/downside decision-making.", "C. cost/benefit analysis.", "D. critical thinking."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Cost/Benefit analysis. Cost/Benefit analysis is a systematic decision-making process that compares the costs of an action to the benefits received. A cost/benefit analysis helps businesspeople make rational, well-informed choices. Upside/Downside decision-making and critical thinking are not methods of economic decision-making. SOURCE: FI:357 SOURCE: LAP-FI-011\u2014Running the Numbers (Cost-Benefit Analysis) Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 21 "}, {"number": 39, "question": "What is a business's debt ratio if it has $360,000 in total debt and $800,000 in total assets? ", "choices": ["A. 40%", "B. 43%", "C. 45%", "D. 46%"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "45%. Debt ratio determines the percentage of debt in relationship to assets. To calculate debt ratio, divide total debt by total assets ($360,000 / $800,000 = .45 or 45%). Therefore, the amount of the business's debt is equal to 45% of its total assets. SOURCE: FI:097 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, March 27). Debt ratio. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/d/debtratio.asp "}, {"number": 40, "question": "Why is it important to ask job applicants about their training and previous job responsibilities during the interview process? ", "choices": ["A. To determine qualifications", "B. To review recommendations", "C. To analyze personality types", "D. To establish specifications"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "To determine qualifications. One of the purposes of the interview process is to determine if job applicants have the qualifications to perform the specific job. To determine this, it is important to ask job applicants about their training and previous job responsibilities. This information will indicate their work experience and education background. Businesses often contact references to verify recommendations. Businesses do not ask job applicants about their training and previous job responsibilities to analyze personality types or to establish specifications. SOURCE: HR:355 SOURCE: Job-Interview-Site.com. (2009-2018). Job interview selection criteria for interviewers. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.job-interview-site.com/how-to-interview-acandidate-selection-criteria-interviewer-tips.html "}, {"number": 41, "question": "Which of the following evaluation tests is usually the most effective in determining the motivation level of prospective employees: ", "choices": ["A. Polygraph", "B. Work sample", "C. Personality and interest", "D. Aptitude and intelligence"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Personality and interest. These tests are used to measure an applicant's motivation and preferences in particular areas. Work samples determine an applicant's skill level. Polygraph tests determine an applicant's truthfulness. Aptitude and intelligence tests are designed to measure a person's natural ability to acquire competence in a particular discipline. SOURCE: HR:356 SOURCE: Meinert, D. (2015, June 1). What do personality tests really reveal? Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.shrm.org/hr-today/news/hr-magazine/pages/0615-personalitytests.aspx "}, {"number": 42, "question": "What do managers do to make sure the work of the business is done effectively and on time? ", "choices": ["A. Supervise staff", "B. Delegate authority", "C. Maintain power", "D. Obtain knowledge"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Supervise staff. Managers are responsible for accomplishing a business's goals which involves making sure work is done effectively and on time. To make sure the work is done, managers supervise staff. This involves overseeing and directing the activities of employees so they will complete the work. Managers delegate authority to others to have time to focus on management responsibilities such as supervising staff. Although managers may delegate authority, they maintain power which enables them to supervise staff. To make sure the work is done, managers share knowledge with employees. SOURCE: HR:393 SOURCE: Kokemuller, N. (2016, October 26). About workplace supervision. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/workplace-supervision-42926.html "}, {"number": 43, "question": "What should a business manager do to effectively handle an employee's complaint? ", "choices": ["A. Explain business procedures", "B. Listen to the complaint", "C. Consider several solutions", "D. Send the employee to counseling"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Consider several solutions. There usually are several ways to solve problems and effectively handle an employee's complaint. Frequently, employees who voice complaints have determined what they consider to be the best solution to the problem. Managers should consider those solutions and encourage employees to participate in developing additional solutions. Managers and employees working together to analyze various solutions will help them to select one that best meets the needs of all the parties involved. Managers need to do more than listen to the complaint; they need to take action to resolve the problem. Explaining business procedures or sending the employee to counseling are not ways of effectively handling an employee's complaint. SOURCE: HR:366 SOURCE: Management Study Guide. (n.d.). Employee grievance - Effective ways of handling grievance. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from ttps://www.managementstudyguide.com/employee-grievance.htm Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 22 "}, {"number": 44, "question": "A piece of easily observable data about a competitor is its ", "choices": ["A. sales reports.", "B. products in development.", "C. current promotional campaign.", "D. future plans."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Current promotional campaign. A competitor's current promotional campaign is shown to the public and is, therefore, easy to observe. However, the products a competitor has in development, along with its sales reports and future plans, may not be public information. This makes them difficult for marketers from competing businesses to learn about. SOURCE: IM:012 SOURCE: LAP-IM-012\u2014Data Do It (Need for Marketing Data) "}, {"number": 45, "question": "Do businesses ever have more than one objective for their marketing-research projects? ", "choices": ["A. Yes, businesses generally combine several marketing-research objectives.", "B. Yes, businesses sometimes have more than one marketing-research objective.", "C. No, businesses set one objective for each marketing-research project.", "D. No, businesses do not have specific marketing-research objectives."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Yes, businesses sometimes have more than one marketing-research objective. Businesses may have one or more than one objective for their research, e.g., exploring a situation and testing solutions. They do not usually combine several objectives as this is not likely to be cost-effective or efficient. SOURCE: IM:010 SOURCE: LAP-IM-010\u2014Seek and Find (Marketing Research) "}, {"number": 46, "question": "If market research yields different results each time it is conducted, the research is not ", "choices": ["A. valid.", "B. reliable.", "C. objective.", "D. systematic."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Reliable. Reliable research brings about the same results when repeated or conducted by different researchers. Valid research measures what the researchers intended to measure. Objective research is free from bias. Systematic research follows a step-by-step process of gathering, recording, and analyzing information. Research can be valid, objective, and systematic without being reliable. SOURCE: IM:010 SOURCE: LAP-IM-010\u2014Seek and Find (Marketing Research) "}, {"number": 47, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a touchpoint: ", "choices": ["A. A company provides new employees with customer-service training.", "B. A customer watches a company's television commercial.", "C. Company management analyzes customer buying behavior.", "D. A company researches customer relationship management software."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "A customer watches a company's television commercial. A touchpoint is any opportunity a company has to connect with its customers and potential customers. Touchpoints include a customer watching a company's television commercial, a customer browsing a company's website, a customer interacting with a salesperson or other company employee, a customer receiving a bill in the mail, etc. A company providing new employees with customer-service training, a company's management analyzing customer buying behavior, and a company researching customer-relationship management software are all situations that indirectly impact customers. However, none are situations in which a company is interacting or connecting directly with its customers and potential customers. SOURCE: MK:019 SOURCE: LAP-MK-003\u2014Just Do It...Right (Company Actions and Results) "}, {"number": 48, "question": "Which of the following is a factor that might make it necessary for a business to change its marketing strategy: ", "choices": ["A. Competition is limited.", "B. Consumers are satisfied.", "C. Technology is advancing.", "D. Economy remains stable."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Technology is advancing. Marketers must be aware that situations can change and be prepared to make changes in marketing strategies when they are needed. Many factors can necessitate a change in marketing strategy, such as advancements in technology. The development of new products or new ways of doing business might make it necessary for a company to change its marketing strategy in order to be successful. If the economy is stable, consumers are satisfied; and if competition is limited, businesses might successfully use the same marketing strategies for many years. SOURCE: MP:001 SOURCE: LAP-MP-002\u2014Pick the Mix (Nature of Marketing Strategies) "}, {"number": 49, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a consumer market: ", "choices": ["A. Workers buying lunch at a local restaurant", "B. Businesses buying vehicles for salespeople", "C. Schools buying chairs for classroom use", "D. Companies buying equipment for a machine shop"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Workers buying lunch at a local restaurant. The consumer market is composed of customers who purchase goods or services to satisfy their personal desires. The other alternatives are examples of the industrial market that purchases items for use in the operation of a business, for resale, or for making other goods. SOURCE: MP:003 SOURCE: LAP-MP-003\u2014Have We Met? (Market Identification) Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 23 "}, {"number": 50, "question": "Age, ethnicity, and income are all factors when developing a target segment based on ", "choices": ["A. demographics.", "B. geography.", "C. behavior.", "D. psychographics."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Demographics. Age, ethnicity, and income are all factors of the science of demographics, which studies the various aspects of a group's background to determine similarities in decision-making of individuals within groups. Sometimes, geographical areas are used to segment populations. This type of targeting can emphasize attachment to a particular geographic location as the defining feature of a group. Behavioral segmentation sorts consumers based on their attitudes toward or use of a product or service. Psychographics is used to segment markets on the basis of beliefs, values, attitudes, lifestyles, etc. SOURCE: MP:004 SOURCE: Marketing Segmentation Study Guide. (2012-2018). Choice of consumer segmentation bases. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://www.segmentationstudyguide.com/segmentation-bases/choice-of-segmentationbases/ "}, {"number": 51, "question": "When a business conducts a market analysis and identifies territories, determines the possible buyers in the territories, and estimates the buyers' purchases, it is evaluating the ", "choices": ["A. competitors' market share.", "B. segment's psychographics.", "C. potential media exposure.", "D. area's market potential."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Area's market potential. A market analysis is a study of a particular market segment. The purpose of the market analysis is to determine the level at which the market segment is willing and able to buy the business's products. One aspect of the market analysis addresses the area market potential, which is the number of potential customers and the potential sales volume for a specific area, territory, or location. Psychographics are lifestyle and personality considerations of a market segment. Competitors are the business's rivals. Media exposure refers to the amount of contact the business makes with the target market through the media (e.g., television, radio). Psychographics, competitors, and media exposure are other important considerations when evaluating the overall market potential of a market segment. SOURCE: MP:009 SOURCE: Arbuckle, D. (2017, September 26). What is \"market potential value?\" Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/info-8040881-market-potential-value.html "}, {"number": 52, "question": "A business has a 30% share of an $845,500 market. What should it forecast in sales for next year's marketing plan if it expects to obtain an additional 5% of the market? ", "choices": ["A. $236,740", "B. $253,650", "C. $270,560", "D. $295,925"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "$295,925. Businesses often forecast sales in dollar amounts. In this example, the business currently has a 30% share of the market but expects to obtain an additional 5% next year. Therefore, next year's market share is expected to be 35% of an $845,500 market. To calculate that amount, multiply the dollar value of the market by the market share ($845,500 X 35% or .35 = $295,925). SOURCE: MP:014 SOURCE: Garner, S. (2013, January 19). The market share method for forecasting sales. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://canadianentrepreneurtraining.com/the-market-sharemethod-for-forecasting-sales/ "}, {"number": 53, "question": "When translating performance measures for marketing activities into financial outcomes, which outcome usually is of most importance to management? ", "choices": ["A. Interest rate", "B. Net profit", "C. Tax level", "D. Unit price"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Net profit. The financial outcomes of marketing activities are of importance to the management of the business. Since it costs money to implement marketing activities, management wants to know if the results are worth the cost involved. An important outcome is net profit, which is the money left after the cost-of-goods expense and the operating expense are each subtracted from the total income. If marketing expenses significantly reduce net profit rather than help increase net profit, management might reevaluate the performance of the marketing activities. Interest rate, tax level, and unit price are not the most important financial outcomes. SOURCE: MP:021 SOURCE: Heneghan, D. (2012, January 18). Key financial outcomes and return on investment ROI. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://customerthink.com/key_financial_outcomes_and_return_on_investment/ Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 24 "}, {"number": 54, "question": "Which of the following software is required for a computer system to be able to access Web data: ", "choices": ["A. Browser", "B. Modem", "C. Filter", "D. Video"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Browser. A browser is a type of software application that allows a user to access Web data. This is an important type of software for businesses that want to access the Web or create their own web pages. There are several browsers available, but the most popular is Google Chrome. A modem is an internal or external computer communications device that is used to transmit information over a particular medium, such as telephone lines or television cables. Filters are computer programs that block out unwanted information. Video software is not required for a computer system to be able to access Web data. SOURCE: NF:012 SOURCE: Orgera, S. (2018, August 22). What is a web browser? Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.lifewire.com/what-is-a-browser-446234 "}, {"number": 55, "question": "By monitoring a variety of sales records on a continuous basis, a business can often develop ", "choices": ["A. selling policies.", "B. training manuals.", "C. distribution lists.", "D. customer profiles."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Customer profiles. Businesses keep their sales records, either manually or on a computer. Sales records provide a lot of information about the business's customers. For example, the business keeps records of its customers' invoices. The invoice provides a lot of information\u2014the customer's address, telephone, a contact name, etc. It also lists the products that the customer orders. By monitoring the types of products that the customer orders, a business can develop a customer profile for the customer, which includes the customer's preferences, purchasing cycles, etc. A comprehensive customer profile can help both the business and its customers to make appropriate purchasing decisions, and can help the business build long-term customer relationships. Monitoring sales records would not help the business develop training manuals, distribution lists, or selling policies. SOURCE: NF:014 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (p. 20). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 56, "question": "A primary reason for a business to interpret statistical findings is to ", "choices": ["A. increase production.", "B. promote creativity.", "C. aid decision-making.", "D. influence buyers."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Aid decision-making. Statistics are information presented in numerical form. For the statistics to be useful, businesses must analyze and interpret them. Businesses often base business decisions on statistical information. For example, a business may obtain statistical information that indicates a product is not selling well. Based on the statistical information, the business may decide to phase out or stop making the product. Or, if statistical information indicates that the demand for the product exceeds the available supply of the product, the business may decide to increase production. Businesses use promotional activities to influence people to buy their products. Although analyzing statistical information might spark an employee's creativity (e.g., for problem-solving purposes), it is not a primary reason for interpreting it. SOURCE: NF:093 SOURCE: Bianca, A. (2016, October 26). The advantage of statistics in business. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://smallbusiness.chron.com/advantages-statistics-business-18698.html "}, {"number": 57, "question": "The function performed by a business in obtaining goods to be resold is ", "choices": ["A. credit.", "B. exchange.", "C. purchasing.", "D. management."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Purchasing. In order for businesses to fulfill their role in the exchange, or transfer process, they must buy goods and then sell them to customers. Credit is the arrangement by which businesses or individuals can purchase now and pay later. Management is the process of planning, organizing, directing, and controlling activities in order to achieve goals or objectives. SOURCE: OP:015 SOURCE: LAP-OP-002\u2014Buy Right (Purchasing) "}, {"number": 58, "question": "Businesses establish efficient operating systems in order to achieve quality and ", "choices": ["A. supervise staff.", "B. monitor production.", "C. expedite workflow.", "D. reduce maintenance."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Expedite workflow. Businesses need operating systems in order to function. Some systems are simple while others are complex, depending on the type and size of the business. However, the goal is for the operating systems to be efficient in order to achieve quality and expedite workflow. The more efficiently and accurately a business operates, the more likely it is to be able to achieve quality. Businesses do not establish efficient operating systems to monitor production, supervise staff, or reduce maintenance. SOURCE: OP:022 SOURCE: Colan, L. (2015, July 1). How to successfully build a business operating system for your company. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.inc.com/lee-colan/building-yourbusiness-operating-system.html Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 25 "}, {"number": 59, "question": "Payroll, rent, utilities, and supplies are all classified as __________ expenses. ", "choices": ["A. contractual", "B. variable", "C. fixed", "D. operating"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Operating. These expenses are the costs incurred in running a business. Operating expenses can be further classified as either fixed or variable. Fixed expenses are set costs for an established period of time, such as rent and utilities. Variable expenses are costs that vary as the sales volume varies. Examples of variable costs are payroll and supplies. Contractual is a distractor. SOURCE: OP:024 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 854-855). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 60, "question": "Conducting a break-even analysis often helps a business ", "choices": ["A. determine market share.", "B. understand the level of demand.", "C. establish a selling price.", "D. monitor the competition."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Establish a selling price. A break-even analysis is a financial analysis whose purpose is to identify the level of sales needed to reach the break-even point at various prices. When conducting a break-even analysis, a business can experiment with different prices to determine the selling price to establish in order to reach the break-even point after a certain level of sales. Conducting a break-even analysis does not help a business understand the level of demand, determine market share, or monitor the competition. SOURCE: OP:192 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (p. 592). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 61, "question": "If a two-year service contract costs $2,900 and can be renewed for the same price and a four-year service contract costs $4,150, how much will a business save by purchasing the four-year contract rather than renewing the two-year contract? ", "choices": ["A. $1,250", "B. $1,450", "C. $1,650", "D. $1,950"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "$1,650. Long-term service contracts are usually less expensive than short-term contracts. However, before purchasing a long-term contract, a business should make sure that it intends to keep the equipment for that length of time. In this example, a two-year contract costs $2,900 as compared to a four-year contract that costs $4,150. However, if the business renews the shorter contract, it will spend more money than if it bought the long-term contract originally. To determine the savings of buying the long-term contract, calculate the price of two short-term contracts ($2,900 X 2 = $5,800). Then, subtract the cost of one long-term contract from this amount to determine the savings ($5,800 - $4,150 = $1,650). SOURCE: OP:027 SOURCE: Rocket Lawyer. (2018). Service contracts. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.rocketlawyer.com/service-contracts.rl "}, {"number": 62, "question": "A budget can be used by a business as a(n) ", "choices": ["A. statement of net worth.", "B. planning and controlling tool.", "C. record of actual expenses.", "D. analysis of income versus expenses."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Planning and controlling tool. Budgets provide projections of income and expenses for a given time period. The budget provides guidelines for a business in planning its operation and controlling its expenses by showing the funds available. An income statement helps the business compare income expenses for a fiscal period. A balance sheet shows a business's assets, liabilities, and net worth. A cash flow statement contains a record of actual expenses. SOURCE: OP:030 SOURCE: Tatum, M., & Harris, B. (2018, November 8). What is budget control? Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.wisegeek.com/what-is-budget-control.htm "}, {"number": 63, "question": "Which of the following supply chain situations is most likely to reduce the cost of a company's products: ", "choices": ["A. Material quality is reduced when using one supplier.", "B. More supply interruption occurs when using one supplier.", "C. Multiple suppliers increase the buyer's negotiation power.", "D. Multiple suppliers make less effort to meet material specifications."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Multiple suppliers increase the buyer's negotiation power. When a buyer uses multiple suppliers, s/he gains more negotiation power to obtain lower supply prices, thereby reducing the cost of a company's products. In addition to the cost of supplies purchased, the labor and time required to produce products also impact product cost. When materials are delayed, unavailable, of poor quality and/or fail to meet material specifications, production rates are reduced and product cost is increased. Relying on one supplier can result in supply interruptions, which can cause a loss in production time and an increase in production costs. When multiple suppliers are used, specific material requirements are less likely to be met, which can increase production time and product cost. SOURCE: OP:303 SOURCE: Research Gate. (n.d.). Advantages and disadvantages of multiple and single sourcing strategy. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from https://www.researchgate.net/figure/Advantages-and-disadvantages-of-multiple-and-singlesourcing-strategy_tbl1_240167996 Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 26 "}, {"number": 64, "question": "A production manager compares March's output goals with the actual outputs that were created for the month. What type of business analysis is the production manager conducting? ", "choices": ["A. Market", "B. Variance", "C. Breakeven", "D. Cash flow"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Variance. A variance is the difference between two variables or factors. The production manager is evaluating the difference between the desired outputs and the actual outputs created. A market analysis assesses factors in the marketplace. A break-even analysis evaluates the level of sales at which revenues equal the total costs. A cash-flow analysis summarizes how money flows into and out of the business. SOURCE: OP:327 SOURCE: Business Analysis Toolkit. (2008-2018). Variance business analysis. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.measurebusiness.com/variance-business-analysis.htm "}, {"number": 65, "question": "When a company uses process thinking to design a process, it should make sure that the process has ", "choices": ["A. an unlimited scope.", "B. a deadline.", "C. multiple process owners.", "D. a goal."], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "A goal. Businesses use process thinking to define and develop a system to accomplish a specific goal or task. Every process should have a goal, and its outputs should be measured against that goal. Each individual process should also support the overall goals of an organization. A process doesn't have a specific deadline since it is a technique used to achieve goals and meet deadlines. Each business process should have a single owner who is responsible for the output and functionality of the process. A business process should have a clearly defined, limited scope. SOURCE: OP:474 SOURCE: Cunningham, W. (2010). Process thinking. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://wcunning.com/DMM/Concepts/Process.html "}, {"number": 66, "question": "A business process design should seek to achieve simplicity because complex designs ", "choices": ["A. require documentation.", "B. must be validated.", "C. result in more errors.", "D. cannot be automated."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Result in more errors. The design of a process should be as simple as possible to avoid unnecessary steps which can cause more errors to occur. Each step in the process should be validated and documented regardless of its simplicity or complexity. Automation should be avoided unless it results in a more efficient process. While it's unadvisable and difficult to automate a complex process, it is not impossible. SOURCE: OP:475 SOURCE: Wallace, O. (2015, December 11). The nine principles of process design. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from https://www.heflo.com/blog/bpm/business-process-designprinciples/ "}, {"number": 67, "question": "The customer service representatives of an auto loan company handle several different types of requests including payments, loan financing, and other general requests. The company determines that the requests are very time consuming when employees aren't familiar with a procedure. The company implements a business process change that requires agents to specialize in particular procedures to increase their efficiency. Which of the following caused this business process change to be made: ", "choices": ["A. Productivity", "B. Quality", "C. Customer experience", "D. Risk management"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Productivity. The company is concerned with the time required to handle customer requests, so the change is made to improve productivity. In the situation described there is no indication that quality of service or customer experience is impacted by the employee's unfamiliarity with procedures. There's no indication that the situation requires the management of risk. SOURCE: OP:476 SOURCE: Spacey, J. (2018 January 16). 9 examples of business process improvement. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from https://simplicable.com/new/business-process-improvement "}, {"number": 68, "question": "A candy shop decides to source most of its candy from one supplier to decrease shipping and transportation costs. How can this supply chain decision negatively impact the shop? ", "choices": ["A. It reduces the number of suppliers that need to be managed.", "B. It increases the cost of the shop's candy products.", "C. It exposes the shop to the risk of product unavailability.", "D. It reduces the amount of advertising that is needed."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "It exposes the shop to the risk of product unavailability. One of the risks of sourcing a large amount of product from one supplier is that products may sometimes be unavailable. When a company sources a large amount of product from one supplier, it typically acquires the product for less. A reduction in advertising is generally determined by a company's business goals and is not typically impacted by changes to suppliers. Reducing the number of suppliers that need to be managed will have a positive impact since business costs are reduced. SOURCE: OP:477 SOURCE: Research Gate. (n.d.). Advantages and disadvantages of multiple and single sourcing strategy. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from https://www.researchgate.net/figure/Advantages-and-disadvantages-of-multiple-and-singlesourcing-strategy_tbl1_240167996 Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 27 "}, {"number": 69, "question": "A company with a small budget has lots of sensitive customer data on file. If it wants to keep this information safe, what should it do? ", "choices": ["A. Focus on prevention by training all employees to protect data", "B. Hire a team of cybersecurity experts", "C. Save money by only teaching one department to protect data", "D. Wait until a breach occurs to develop a protection plan"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Focus on prevention by training all employees to protect data. Keeping data safe and protected requires a company-wide focus on security. This means training all employees to use practices that protect customer and company data. This sort of training should be conducted before a breach ever occurs. Hiring a team of cybersecurity experts would be unrealistic for a company with a small budget. The company should not teach only one department to protect data as a cost-saving measure. If a breach occurs because some employees were not trained, the company will end up spending a lot more money in the long run. SOURCE: OP:472 SOURCE: Motta, F. (2015, March 16). Strategies to help your business thwart cyber attacks, protect systems and secure digital assets. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://www.risbj.com/strategies-to-help-your-business-thwart-cyber-attacks-protect-systemsand-secure-digital-assets/ "}, {"number": 70, "question": "Which of the following steps in the decision-making process involves determining the consequences of taking different actions: ", "choices": ["A. Stating the problem", "B. Identifying resources", "C. Collecting data", "D. Evaluating information"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Evaluating information. Individuals should evaluate the information they have gathered and identify the pros and cons of taking different actions. They should look at the consequences of all possible decisions and review what might happen based on the information they have obtained. Stating the problem, collecting data, and identifying resources for action are not part of identifying the consequences of taking these different actions. SOURCE: PD:017 SOURCE: LAP-PD-017\u2014Weigh Your Options (Decision-Making) "}, {"number": 71, "question": "Which of the following best describes the purpose of corporate governance: ", "choices": ["A. To ensure that companies are held to high ethical standards", "B. To create a favorable image for the company", "C. To make hiring and firing decisions for entry-level employees", "D. To improve relations with company stockholders"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "To ensure that companies are held to high ethical standards. Corporate governance is important because it holds companies accountable for their behavior and helps organizations avoid financial, legal, and ethical pitfalls. The purpose of corporate governance is not to create a favorable image for the company, to make hiring and firing decisions for entry-level employees, or to improve relations with company stockholders. SOURCE: PD:213 SOURCE: IAC Publishing, LLC. (2015, August 4). Why is corporate governance important? Retrieved November 26, 2018, from https://www.reference.com/business-finance/corporategovernance-important-6f7173fe92e0b495# "}, {"number": 72, "question": "Rahul, the CEO of a large corporation, needs to make sure his management team complies with the new governance practices. What is the best way for Rahul to ensure the management team knows how to comply? ", "choices": ["A. Verbally define roles and responsibilities", "B. Select a new board of directors", "C. Define roles and responsibilities in writing", "D. Evaluate performance of the board of directors"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Define roles and responsibilities in writing. To make sure the management team and all other stakeholders know how to comply with governance practices, each stakeholder should be given clear roles and responsibilities in writing\u2014not just verbally. Selecting a new board of directors or evaluating the performance of the board will not ensure the management team complies with governance practices. SOURCE: PD:214 SOURCE: McInnes Cooper (2014, September 16). The top 5 corporate governance best practices that benefit every company. Retrieved November 26, 2018, from http://www.mcinnescooper.com/publications/legal-update-the-top-5-corporate-governancebest-practices-that-benefit-every-company/ "}, {"number": 73, "question": "Which of the following is an internal factor that impacts corporate governance structures: ", "choices": ["A. Independent audits", "B. Regulation", "C. Segregation of duties", "D. Industry association guidelines"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Segregation of duties. Segregation of duties is a concept that refers to more than one person completing a task. Segregating duties helps companies avoid errors and misconduct that could be committed by one individual. Companies that institute segregation of duties are strengthening their corporate governance structures. Regulation, independent audits, and industry association guidelines are all external factors that affect corporate governance structures. SOURCE: PD:302 SOURCE: Davoren, J. (2017, November 21). Three types of corporate governance mechanisms. Retrieved November 23, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/three-types-corporategovernance-mechanisms-66711.html Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 28 "}, {"number": 74, "question": "TRISM Co. sets an organizational goal to gain 100 new clients. To do so, each sales rep must contact five prospects per week. This is an example of ", "choices": ["A. designing an organizational structure.", "B. aligning personal goals with company goals.", "C. establishing performance standards.", "D. generating new product ideas."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Establishing performance standards. Performance standards are mechanisms used to track, monitor, and measure success. When employees have performance standards that are aligned with organizational goals, it is much more likely that the company will accomplish those goals. Contacting five prospects per week is a performance standard that is in line with TRISM Co.'s organizational goals. This is not an example of aligning personal goals with company goals, designing an organizational structure, or generating new product ideas. SOURCE: PD:256 SOURCE: Gallo, A. (2011, February 20). Making sure your employees succeed. Retrieved November 23, 2018, from https://hbr.org/2011/02/making-sure-your-employees-suc "}, {"number": 75, "question": "Business A spends less on advertising than Business B. Both businesses sell the same products, but Business B charges higher prices than Business ", "choices": ["", "B. Both businesses sell the same products, but\nBusiness B charges higher prices than Business A. Which of the following factors has affected the prices\nof the business:\nA. Place\nB. Supply", "C. Product", "D. Promotion"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Promotion. Business B is spending more on its advertising and is passing the costs on to the customer through higher prices. Place involves getting products in the right place at the right time. Product decisions involve deciding what goods, services, or ideas to produce or to sell in order to satisfy customers' needs and wants. Supply is the quantity of a good or service that sellers are able and willing to offer for sale at a specified price in a given time period. SOURCE: PI:001 SOURCE: LAP-PI-002\u2014The Price Is Right (Nature of Pricing) "}, {"number": 76, "question": "What pricing objective would be most effective for a new business that wants to establish a market share, be competitive, and create a specific image? ", "choices": ["A. Return on sales percentage", "B. Sales-oriented pricing", "C. Profit-oriented pricing", "D. Return on investment percentage"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Sales-oriented pricing. Sales-oriented pricing objectives can be used to create a company image, be more competitive, and influence market share. These objectives are intended to increase a business's total amount of income from sales. Profit-oriented price objectives focus on creating profits for the business. Return on investment and return on sales are aspects of profit-oriented pricing objectives and focus on creating profits for the business. SOURCE: PI:002 SOURCE: LAP-PI-003\u2014Make Cents (Factors Affecting Selling Price) "}, {"number": 77, "question": "One reason why the target market of a business affects its pricing is because consumers in each target market ", "choices": ["A. expect a large product mix.", "B. judge the value of products differently.", "C. prefer products in the growth stage.", "D. monitor the industry standard."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Judge the value of products differently. The target market of a business affects its pricing because, even in the same market, not all customers see price from the same point of view. Some customers see low price as an indicator of low quality, while others see low price as a bargain. Or, some customers see high price as an indicator of high quality, while others see it as a poor value for the price. Therefore, businesses need to determine what price range will be accepted in their markets. Consumers in each target market do not necessarily expect a large product mix, prefer products in the growth stage, or monitor the industry standard. SOURCE: PI:002 SOURCE: LAP-PI-003\u2014Make Cents (Factors Affecting Selling Price) "}, {"number": 78, "question": "Which of the following questions do businesses ask when they evaluate the feasibility of a product idea: ", "choices": ["A. Does this product satisfy the company's needs?", "B. How can we come up with innovative ideas for more products?", "C. Do we have access to the resources to make this product?", "D. Will vendors buy or use the product if it is available?"], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Do we have access to the resources to make this product? Product research and development is an expensive process for a business. Before a business invests time, personnel, and money to take an idea and turn it into a product, it must determine if it has the resources to make the product. If the product requires more resources than the company has access to, it may be impossible to make and market the product. The question about coming up with more product ideas is part of the idea generation process. Questions about needs' satisfaction and willingness to buy the product should relate to the customers rather than the business or its vendors. SOURCE: PM:129 SOURCE: Business Queensland. (2018, July 12). Feasibility analysis. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.business.qld.gov.au/starting-business/planning/idea/feasibility Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 29 "}, {"number": 79, "question": "A product mix with product lines that are closely related in terms of the products' end use, methods of distribution and production, target market(s), and/or price range would be described as having ", "choices": ["A. consistency.", "B. depth.", "C. width.", "D. class."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Consistency. If the products in a company's product lines are closely related on any one of these factors, the product mix is said to be consistent. Depth refers to the number of products and the assortment of sizes, colors, and models in the product line. Width refers to the number of product lines carried by a company. Product class is one of the ways in which a business can set up its product lines. SOURCE: PM:003 SOURCE: LAP-PM-003\u2014Mix & Match (The Nature of the Product Mix) "}, {"number": 80, "question": "What do businesses often provide to customers in order to develop and maintain a competitive advantage over other businesses? ", "choices": ["A. Discount coupons", "B. Free services", "C. Free samples", "D. Instant rebates"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Free services. Many companies provide free services to customers as a routine part of doing business. One reason for providing free services, such as delivery, is to develop and maintain a competitive advantage over other similar businesses. If everything else is equal, customers often buy from the businesses that give them free services rather than from businesses that do not offer those services or that charge for the services. Free samples, discount coupons, and instant rebates are promotional techniques that might attract customers at first but do not help businesses to maintain a competitive advantage. SOURCE: PM:036 SOURCE: Skok, D. (2015, November 3). The power of free. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.forentrepreneurs.com/power-of-free/ "}, {"number": 81, "question": "You should base your USP on reliable research into your company's target market's ", "choices": ["A. needs and wants.", "B. religion and work experience.", "C. race and education.", "D. age and gender."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Needs and wants. You should base your USP on reliable research into your target market's needs and wants. Demographics such as religion, work experience, race, education, age, and gender all determine what those needs and wants are\u2014but you just need to know the needs and wants to work on your USP. SOURCE: PM:272 SOURCE: LAP-PM-016\u2014Stand Out (Unique Selling Proposition) "}, {"number": 82, "question": "In promotional communication, the feedback that buyers (consumers) give to senders (businesses) is usually in the form of ", "choices": ["A. purchases.", "B. complaints.", "C. referrals.", "D. suggestions."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Purchases. Promotion is the communication of information about goods, services, images, and/or ideas to achieve a desired outcome. Businesses use promotion to inform buyers about goods and services in order to encourage them to buy. By purchasing the goods or services, buyers give feedback to senders. Buyers let the senders know that they received the promotional message and respond by making purchases. A complaint is a customer's expression of a dissatisfaction. A suggestion is a recommendation. Referrals are individuals or businesses to whom salespeople are recommended. SOURCE: PR:001 SOURCE: LAP-PR-002\u2014Razzle Dazzle (Nature of Promotion) "}, {"number": 83, "question": "Repeated exposure to the largest, most diverse population of people is a benefit of ___________ advertising. ", "choices": ["A. newspaper", "B. out-of-home", "C. directory", "D. radio"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Out-of-home. Certain spots (e.g., bus stations) outside of the home attract a large percentage of people from different backgrounds, thereby providing the perfect opportunity to expose them to a message over and over again. Radio advertisements last for only as long as they are on the air, and they are targeted at a very specific group of listeners. Once people are finished reading newspapers, they typically throw them away. In addition, not as many people read newspapers as drive by public places over and over again. Directory advertising is a great opportunity to appeal to people who are looking for the business's contact information, but rarely is there repeated exposure to an ad. SOURCE: PR:007 SOURCE: LAP-PR-003\u2014Ad-quipping Your Business (Types of Advertising Media) Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 30 "}, {"number": 84, "question": "Alexandria has been using Look-So-Good cosmetics for several years and would not consider changing brands. In fact, Alexandria likes the cosmetics so much that she has become an advocate for the cosmetic company. She tells everyone about the features and benefits of Look-So-Good products, and encourages them to try the cosmetics. What type of word-of-mouth marketing is Alexandria using? ", "choices": ["A. Organic marketing", "B. Mobile marketing", "C. Shill marketing", "D. Virtual marketing"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Organic marketing. Word-of-mouth promotion occurs when customers tell others about their satisfaction with the business. Organic word-of-mouth promotion occurs naturally. Because customers are satisfied with the business and its products, they enthusiastically tell others about their satisfaction in the course of normal conversation. In some situations, customers trust and like the product so much that they become product advocates\u2014putting in a good word whenever and wherever they can. Virtual marketing involves communicating product information via the Internet. Mobile marketing involves communicating information via mobile devices and networks (e.g., smartphones). Shill marketing involves employing people to pose as customers who are satisfied with a business's product using word-of-mouth techniques. Shill marketing is unethical behavior, and in some jurisdictions, it is an illegal practice. SOURCE: PR:247 SOURCE: Warren, M. (2018, October 25). Word of mouth marketing in 2018: How to create a strategy for social media buzz & skyrocket referral sales. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.bigcommerce.com/blog/word-of-mouth-marketing/#what-is-word-of-mouthmarketing "}, {"number": 85, "question": "Postcards, catalogs, and sales letters are forms of ", "choices": ["A. mass communication.", "B. publicity.", "C. direct mail.", "D. public relations."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Direct mail. Direct mail is a promotional medium that comes to consumers' homes and businesses in the form of letters, catalogs, postcards, faxes, and folders. Publicity is any nonpersonal presentation of ideas, goods, or services that is not paid for by the company or individual that benefits from or is harmed by it. Television and radio commercials and newspaper and magazine advertisements are examples of mass communication, which consists of nonpersonal promotional messages. The function of business designed to establish good relations between the business and the public is public relations. SOURCE: PR:089 SOURCE: Mail Shark. (2018). What is direct mail marketing? Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.themailshark.com/resources/articles/what-is-direct-mail-marketing/ "}, {"number": 86, "question": "Which of the following is a type of sales promotion that provides customers with immediate rewards: ", "choices": ["A. Price-off deals", "B. Mail-in rebates", "C. Loyalty programs", "D. Product displays"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Price-off deals. Price-off deals involve discounting the prices of goods and services for a short period of time. Because customers save money by buying the products during the sale, they receive an immediate reward\u2014a good or service that they want or need at a discounted price. A rebate is a return of part of the price a customer pays for a good or service and usually is offered by the product's manufacturer. Loyalty programs reward repeat customers by offering incentives (e.g., free item) to maintain their loyalty to the business. Although rebates and loyalty programs provide rewards, customers must usually wait to receive them. Product displays exhibit merchandise and do not provide rewards. SOURCE: PR:249 SOURCE: Clow, K.E, & Baack, D. (2010). Integrated advertising, promotion, and marketing communications (4th ed.) [pp. 337-338]. Upper Saddle River, NJ: Prentice Hall. "}, {"number": 87, "question": "What interactive communication channel do businesses use to share company information with their various publics? ", "choices": ["A. Press releases", "B. Blogs", "C. Newsletters", "D. Video releases"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Blogs. A blog is an online diary or journal. Businesses use blogs as an informal way to share company news, awards, research findings, trends, \"how-to\" information, product updates and uses with their various publics. Blogs are interactive when they have applications that allow readers to post comments or respond to blog postings. The ability to obtain feedback from blog readers is helpful to businesses in gauging public opinion about their activities. Press releases, newslettters, and video releases are communication methods used to share public relations information; however, these are not interactive communication methods. SOURCE: PR:250 SOURCE: Eyo, I. (2016, July 25). 3 reasons why blogging is an excellent public relations tool. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from https://ducttapemarketingconsultant.com/blogging-ispublic-relations-tool/ Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 31 "}, {"number": 88, "question": "Which of the following situations is an example of a public relations activity: ", "choices": ["A. Jana prepares a press release about her firm's new licensing agreement with a large company.", "B. Evan coordinates an upcoming sales promotion with the company's purchasing manager.", "C. Colleen telephones a prospective customer to try to schedule a product demonstration.", "D. Eli reviews a report to determine which clients have overdue payments due on their accounts."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Jana prepares a press release about her firm's new licensing agreement with a large company. The public relations department is the area of the business that is responsible for establishing good relations between the business and the public. Public relations staff members are responsible for developing and distributing press releases. Press releases include newsworthy information about the business and are provided to the media to obtain publicity. Businesses often distribute press releases to announce new products, employee promotions, mergers, awards, licensing agreements, etc. Sales promotion is a product-promotion activity. Calling on prospective customers to schedule product demonstrations is a sales activity. Reviewing an overdue-accounts report is an accounting activity. SOURCE: PR:252 SOURCE: Farese, L.S., Kimbrell, G., & Woloszyk, C.A. (2012). Marketing essentials (pp. 397-399). Columbus, OH: Glencoe/McGraw-Hill. "}, {"number": 89, "question": "One of the most important characteristics of a quality good is ", "choices": ["A. reliability.", "B. tangibles.", "C. empathy.", "D. responsiveness."], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Reliability. One of the most important characteristics of a quality good is reliability. Customers are looking for products they can count on. Empathy, tangibles, and responsiveness are characteristics that customers seek in a quality service provider. SOURCE: QM:001 SOURCE: LAP-QM-001\u2014Keep It Quality (Nature of Quality Management) "}, {"number": 90, "question": "Why does a company need to have clearly stated business objectives to accurately identify risk? ", "choices": ["A. Clearly stated business objectives can effectively eliminate all identified business risks.", "B. Clearly stated business objectives determine whether the company will achieve the desired\namount of profit.", "C. Developing clearly stated business objectives is the main activity of designing an overall risk\nmanagement strategy.", "D. Having clearly stated business objectives makes it easier to identify the actual importance of"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Having clearly stated business objectives makes it easier to identify the actual importance of specific risks. Risk management involves identifying, analyzing, and evaluating potential risks so they can be effectively managed. When a company's business objectives are clearly stated, it is easier to identify how important a specific risk is. Achieving a desired amount of profit is dependent on many factors and is not achieved solely by identifying risk or developing clearly stated business objectives. Developing clearly stated business objectives is just one activity involved in designing an overall risk management strategy. An overall risk management strategy is a complex and strategic business management tool that has many important components (e.g., risk assessment matrix analysis and formal contingency plans) to reduce actual risks. Since business risks are an inherent part of conducting business, it is impossible to eliminate them\u2014no matter how clearly stated the company's business objectives are. SOURCE: RM:044 SOURCE: Moore, A. (2016, November 16). Risk management: Alignment to the business objectives. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/risk-managementalignment-business-objectives-andrew-moore/ "}, {"number": 91, "question": "A company that processes electronic financial payments has discovered that some of its employees with drug problems have stolen customers' banking information to commit fraud. What type of business risk created this negative situation? ", "choices": ["A. Human risk", "B. Technology risk", "C. Strategy risk", "D. Financial risk"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Human risk. A problem caused by employees is considered a human risk. Drug abuse is a major human risk that employers must deal with and that can lead to employee absence, theft, and fraud. Technology risks involve power outages and failure of devices such as computers, phones, routers, satellites, etc. Strategy risks are risks related to or caused by an organization's business objectives. Financial risk typically refers to risks associated with a company's capital structure and financing, such as exposure to loan default or the inability to collect returns on an investment. SOURCE: RM:056 SOURCE: Davis, M. (2018, February 13). Identifying and managing business risks. Retrieved November 20, 2018, from http://www.investopedia.com/articles/financial-theory/09/riskmanagement-business.asp "}, {"number": 92, "question": "Which of the following is an example of an external factor that has increased interest in enterprise risk management (ERM): ", "choices": ["A. Increased regulatory scrutiny", "B. Decreased transparency", "C. Increased efficiency", "D. Decreased volume of information"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Increased regulatory scrutiny. With greater attention placed on compliance and risk-management policies, companies have turned to enterprise risk management to help them manage the vast number of risks that could affect them. Decreased transparency, increased efficiency, and decreased volume of information are not factors that have increased interest in enterprise risk management. SOURCE: RM:062 SOURCE: Investopedia. (2018, July 1). Enterprise risk management. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.investopedia.com/terms/e/enterprise-risk-management.asp Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 32 "}, {"number": 93, "question": "How does selling benefit the private enterprise economic system? ", "choices": ["A. Contributes to unemployment", "B. Adds utility to products", "C. Eliminates competition", "D. Increases prices of products"], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Adds utility to products. Selling adds utility, or usefulness, to products. Through selling, products can be in the right place, at the right time. This makes it easy for customers to buy which, in turn, keeps the economy growing. In a private enterprise system, selling usually helps reduce unemployment, promote competition, and keep prices from increasing. SOURCE: SE:017 SOURCE: LAP-SE-117\u2014Sell Away (The Nature and Scope of Selling) "}, {"number": 94, "question": "When faced with an ethical dilemma, a manager should consider the impact that her/his actions and decisions will have on ", "choices": ["A. pay raises, employees, and society.", "B. pay raises, bonuses, and the company's profits.", "C. employees, society, and the company's profits.", "D. suppliers, employees, and society."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Employees, society, and the company's profits. To make ethical decisions, managers should consider the impact that their actions will have on their employees, the society, and their companies' profits. Managers have an obligation to all three. They must look after the welfare of their employees, they have a moral responsibility to protect the greater society, and they must help their companies to be as profitable as possible. Pay raises, bonuses, and suppliers are not necessarily things that managers need to consider when faced with an ethical dilemma. In fact, managers may make more ethical decisions when financial rewards are not taken into consideration. SOURCE: SM:002 SOURCE: Leonard, K. (2018, October 19). What are managerial ethics? Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://smallbusiness.chron.com/managerial-ethics-36425.html "}, {"number": 95, "question": "In what way can an existing business benefit from writing a business plan? ", "choices": ["A. Determine how to distribute profits", "B. Begin operations", "C. Identify managers' roles", "D. Acquire funding for a new idea"], "answer": "D", "reasoning": "Acquire funding for a new idea. Existing businesses know that putting a new idea (such as an expanded sales force) into action requires money\u2014and that a business plan can help bankers and investors determine how involved they want to be. Existing businesses have already begun operations and identified managers' roles (whether formally or informally). A business plan is seldom used to determine how to distribute profits. SOURCE: SM:007 SOURCE: LAP-SM-007\u2014Plan Now, Succeed Later (Nature of Business Plans) "}, {"number": 96, "question": "Managers use the broad objectives they develop for a business as the basis for setting ", "choices": ["A. benefit levels.", "B. performance targets.", "C. salary ranges.", "D. recruitment quotas."], "answer": "B", "reasoning": "Performance targets. Managers develop broad objectives for a business, such as operate in a costefficient manner or earn a sufficient profit. They use these objectives as the basis for setting performance targets. The performance targets are the specific steps a business follows in order to achieve its main objectives. If the main objective is to earn a sufficient profit, the performance targets might include establishing policies to control spending. A business's broad objectives are not used as the basis for setting benefit levels, salary ranges, or recruitment quotas. SOURCE: SM:008 SOURCE: Wascher, K. (2017, September 26). How to write business goals & objectives. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://bizfluent.com/how-6327559-write-business-goalsobjectives.html "}, {"number": 97, "question": "Which of the following is a promotion-related question that a business might ask in order to adjust its marketing mix in response to environmental changes: ", "choices": ["A. What laws affect our advertising?", "B. To whom should we offer discounts?", "C. Is our product aimed at a specific market?", "D. Which channels of distribution will we use?"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "What laws affect our advertising? This is a promotion-related question because advertising is a form of promotion. All businesses need to be familiar with the laws forbidding deceptive practices in advertising. Asking to whom we should offer discounts is a price-related question. Asking whether the product is aimed at a specific market is a product-related question. Asking what channels of distribution will be used is a place-related question. SOURCE: SM:011 SOURCE: Riley, J. (2018). External environment: Introduction (GCSE). Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.tutor2u.net/business/reference/external-environment-introduction Test 1197 ENTREPRENEURSHIP AND SMALL BUSINESS MANAGEMENT EXAM\u2014KEY 33 "}, {"number": 98, "question": "Which of the following technologies do many businesses use to monitor key performance indicators: ", "choices": ["A. Dashboards", "B. Firewalls", "C. Extranets", "D. Terabytes"], "answer": "A", "reasoning": "Dashboards. Dashboards are types of computer-generated, custom-designed reports that indicate the overall situation of a business. They present a set of key performance indicators that, when viewed together, give a snapshot of the health of the company. Managers use dashboards to track the condition of the company and identify potential problems so they can make adjustments before any harm is done. Firewalls, extranets, and terabytes are not used to monitor key performance indicators. SOURCE: SM:027 SOURCE: Karlson, K. (2015, November 17). What is a KPI tracking dashboard? The complete guide. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.scoro.com/blog/what-is-kpi-trackingdashboard/ "}, {"number": 99, "question": "Which of the following statements accurately describes the relationship among innovation, learning, and change: ", "choices": ["A. New learning triggers innovation, leading to internal and external changes.", "B. Innovation triggers internal and external changes, leading to new learning.", "C. Internal and external changes trigger new learning, leading to innovation.", "D. Internal and external changes trigger innovation, leading to new learning."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Internal and external changes trigger new learning, leading to innovation. Both internal and external changes trigger the need for companies to learn and adapt to new situations and trends, resulting in innovation. The other alternatives incorrectly describe the relationship among innovation, learning, and change. SOURCE: SM:094 SOURCE: Decision Innovation. (2009-2018). Managing change and innovation: Getting the most from the innovation funnel. Retrieved November 21, 2018, from http://www.innovationmanagement.org/managing-change-and-innovation.html "}, {"number": 100, "question": "Company executives decided to add a new product line to the company's mix. The company would benefit from ", "choices": ["A. adjusting its budget.", "B. hiring new employees.", "C. change management.", "D. ethics training."], "answer": "C", "reasoning": "Change management. Change management is a structured process used to ensure that changes are successfully made and have lasting impact. Change management would be beneficial to a company that is adding a new product line. There is no indication that the company needs to hire new employees, adjust its budget, or undergo ethics training. SOURCE: SM:095 SOURCE: Prosci. (n.d.). What is change management and how does it work? Retrieved November 21, 2018, from https://www.prosci.com/resources/articles/the-what-why-and-how-of-changemanagemen"}],"1167-ENT-DISTRIC":[],"1167-ENT-DISTRI":[]}